If you were tasked with making the world
believe that Jeffrey Epstein was dead
and getting him out of that prison
[clears throat] without anyone knowing
to wherever he's going to go to get
facial surgery and live out his life,
how would you do it? Oh, you would take
out the body, whether it's a a body
double or, you know, made out of
silicone or whatever. Take it out in
full view of everybody. [snorts]
That's how I would do it.
Let as many people as possible see this
body
so that reasonable people can agree to
disagree.
They did do that.
>> Mhm.
>> Hello, I'm John Kuryaku and I'm here to
[__] [__] up.
>> [music]
>> You're like the most famous guy on the
internet now. I don't recognize your
normal voice. It's killing me.
>> I know, right? [laughter]
I don't know how this happened.
It just happened. Like literally
overnight. It just happened. [laughter]
Can we pull up the latest one that we
put up, thief? Yeah.
>> Let's get John's live reaction. So, when
this was happening, when you and I did
episodes 278 and 279 together, which was
a year ago, [laughter]
>> I remember this was probably like an
hour 20ome minutes into the first
episode, and I remember this whole
Lincoln thing coming up out of nowhere.
Like, ah this is cool. He's a Lincoln
collector. And then you look at me with
a dead straight face and you're like,
yeah, I was trying to buy Lincoln's last
turd. And I at the time we had Allessie
in the studio and I'm I'm I'm like
turning to Allessie like this this
[__] get the series and then
you're like oh yeah I was trying to buy
it. So when this all started to break
like Danny on on our editing team and
and I were we're were looking at stuff
I'm like you got to make the Lincoln
[__] [laughter] star. So he he did.
Let's run it.
>> Can people see this Steve?
>> Yeah.
>> All right let's roll.
>> Show museum. And it was a museum of
circus freak shows from the 1800s and
stuff that had been in these circus
sideesh shows. They have the shadow box
hanging on the wall and there's a
>> dried out turd
>> and it says it's
>> Abraham Lincoln's final turd.
>> Come on. So it says on the card it said
when he arrived at Ford's Theater he had
to drop a deuce and so before he got
seated he went to the men's room
>> and he dropped a deuce in the chamber
pot
>> and then he went back to watch the play
>> and he got shot.
>> Somebody had the presence of mind
>> and they say presence in mind
>> for the sickness. Well,
>> but there are a lot of linking
collector. [laughter]
>> I see an article in the Washington Post
about six months later saying it's going
out of business and they're going to
auction everything off. So, I told my
wife,
>> I'm buying that tur.
>> She's like,
>> "Oh, no you're not."
>> And I said, "Oh, yes, I am. I'm buying
that tur."
>> My [clears throat] wife and I actually
have strong disagreements about this. We
go to the auction and I
>> I top out at 1,200 bucks.
>> It ends up going for five grand. So, the
guy that ended up buying it sends it to
some company for a DNA sample. And what
they found was it had like microscopic
bits of a necafer in it. But necro
wafers weren't invented until 1880.
>> It wasn't a [__] It wasn't his. Some
random guy's turn
$5,000
for. [laughter]
>> That is one of my better stories. Oh my
god. Are you familiar with Black Twitter
at all?
>> No.
>> Oh, you're not? You need to familiarize
yourself. They love you.
Yo, this [__] John crazy. Yo,
[laughter] this some words I'm not
allowed to say. This [__] out
here just saying straight cat, but it's
real. [laughter] And I'm I'm [__]
dying reading this.
>> And I'm telling you, it happened
literally overnight.
>> Yeah.
>> And I don't understand why.
>> I know you don't. I mean, you're like,
for people that don't know you
personally, which is pretty much
everyone out [laughter] there listening,
like you've lived this amazing life and
done all all these incredible things or
whatever, but it's always funny to talk
to you like about content cuz you're
like, "Oh, was that good?" I'm like,
[laughter] "Yeah, John, like 15 million
views on something's really good." And
you're like, "Okay." And you leave
[laughter]
and we're just like, "You know what?
You're happy as a clam. We'll keep it
that way."
>> And you know, some crazy stuff has
happened since I saw you last. I've got
this great friend, Tyrell Vanto, Jesse
Vanto's son. Ty is one of the sweetest
men I've ever I've ever met. He's just a
really good-hearted, kind guy. What's
up, guys? Three quick things. Number
one, if you have not already subscribed,
please hit that subscribe button. It is
a huge, huge help. Number two, if you'd
like to join my Patreon for early
uncensored releases of these episodes,
you can join via the link in my
description or my pin comment. And
number three, if you'd like to join my
clipping community for a chance to edit
clips from the show and make money, you
can join via the Discord link in my
description below. And he calls me one
night in July.
And uh and he says uh he wrote a movie
and Tai's Tai's a Hollywood guy. He's
he's done a lot in in film. He wrote
this movie. I was like, "Oh, that's
cool. Good for you." And he said, "Well,
you know, it's going to be this is the
story." I was like, "Yeah, that actually
sounds like a compelling story line."
[laughter]
And I'm thinking, "Why [clears throat]
is he telling me this? I'm happy for
him. He's going to write this movie."
And he said, "Uh, you're going to be in
my movie." [laughter] And I said, "Oh,
thank you. No, no, no. I'm not
interested." I said, "Listen, I'll be
stiff and uh unconvincing. I'm I would
be a terrible actor. I've never acted
before and I would wreck your movie."
And he said, 'Well, I thought of that
and I thought you've been you acted
every day of your career when you were
with the CIA. I said, 'Well, that's
actually that's actually true. And he
said, "So, I wrote the part specifically
for you and you're going to be in the
movie." So, I went to Mexico for the
whole month of October.
>> Wow.
>> And we filmed this movie and I'm very
proud to say that I am now a member of
the Screen Actors Guild.
>> Oh, you're in SAG now. [laughter]
That's not suspicious at all. CIA guy in
SAG.
>> I'm also now a professional Hollywood
actor.
>> Were you Did you feel like you were good
at it when you were doing it? I feel
like you're a natural.
>> No, I listen. Everybody around me,
everybody else in the film was
incredible. Like I would stand there
just off camera watching them in awe of
their ability to do this over and over
and over again. scene. We would do each
scene eight, 10, 12 times
>> and they were so good. And they've all
been in stuff. They've all been in
movies and TV series and all kinds of
stuff. And then the star of the movie is
a a a really great guy, very generous
with his time and his advice. Uh Jeff
Fehee,
>> I really hit it off with him.
He would stand just off camera and
whisper directions to me and it made me
like I guess believable enough that I
didn't make an ass of myself in this
movie. So we watched the first cut a
couple of Saturdays ago
>> and I was like this movie's actually
good.
>> Like I would go to the theater to watch
it.
>> What's it What's it about? It's about
the richest guy in the world who's a
cross between Elon Musk and um and uh
Eric Prince and
he has a son who has become his daughter
and so they're estranged and he hasn't
told anybody but he's dying of liver
cancer
>> and so he invites the the country's
preeminent
lefty podcaster and the country's
preeminent righty podcaster to come and
he's going to tell his story for the
first time and then they sort of are
competing with one another how they're
going to shape the story. One falls
apart, the other one gets it done and
then I'm the director of the guy's
security detail. Uh former CIA ops
officer.
>> Oh, right on Q. There [laughter] you go.
But you had to play a bit of a tough
guy, right?
>> Yeah, I had to play an [__] The guy
was an [__]
>> and a liar.
>> You couldn't play that? I was in a
dumpster all night.
>> [laughter]
>> That's another one that's faking the
rounds. Do I smell like I've been with a
woman [laughter]
>> and then the best is they switch it back
and your voice like we later got
divorced [laughter]
[__] let Oh my god. Oh, they start
crying.
>> Oh, well that's very good. I'm I'm glad
you're in SAG now. So I just add it to
the resume, right?
>> Last night I cast my votes for the SAG
awards now now called the actor awards.
>> Excellent.
>> I took it very seriously. They they they
send everybody. They're like, you know,
50 million people that are in the SAG,
so it it's not like, you know, this was
anything necessarily special. It was for
me. So, they send you the list of
nominees. They send you links to every
one of the movies and the TV series. I
watched every last one of them
>> and I cast educated votes. [laughter]
>> Good for you, John. Someone's taking it
seriously. They need your type in there.
>> That's right. But we we are we are here
obviously as like kind of an emergency
episode because of what's going on and I
know you have
>> some stuff that you heard whispers in
the wind if you will about Iran. So we
will get to that a little bit later but
I definitely want to start on the story
of my lifetime I think is what I would
say at this point. You and I have talked
about it in the past on episodes with
Epstein and you know how they've slowly
rolled out this case and people have
found out information over the years and
now there's some files coming out and
there's a lot of issues there. But I got
to tell you, man,
reading through these emails,
>> yeah,
>> sickening. There are so many things that
in the past people might have presented
to me, random people with, let's say, no
evidence that I was like, "Come on."
>> Yeah.
>> I've done the same thing. That's been my
response. Like, come on. You have
evidence.
>> Now, when you read it, are you like me
where you're like, "Well, I can't rule
this out anymore."
>> I will say I've got a great friend, Ben
Swan, terrific investigative journalist
who was laser focused on Pizzagate. And
Pizzagate always sounded so insane to me
that I was like, "Come on, man. What are
you doing? You're going to kill your
career with this Pizzagate thing." First
of all, the pizza place doesn't even
have a basement where they're keeping
kids, right? And this clown from North
Carolina drives up with an AR-15 or
whatever it was, AK-47, and shoots the
place up. And then he can't find a
basement where the kids are being kept
as sex slaves, and he, you know, gives
himself up. And then we see these emails
last week about, you know, take a Viagra
and then we'll go get some pizza and
grape soda. Haha.
It's It's nuts.
>> I can't believe it in some of these
cases.
>> And the, you know, the the the code word
usage. The the other thing, John, that's
so sinister is
it's almost like it was a giant, you
know, [__] you meme to everyone. like
the worst sadistic kind because you have
a guy emailing from account from an
account called J E Vacation. Like you
can't even make this up. That's like
what your grandpa would make on an auto
AOL account back in 1999 when he wanted
to be hip and make an email.
>> Mhm.
>> You know what I mean? And they talk so
flippantly, like forget the most
sadistic stuff where they're talking
about
>> children and the awful things they're
doing to them
>> like that. But they talk so flippantly
about the world. And it had me
rethinking what George Carlin once said.
I always quote it. Everyone always
quotes it. It's a big club and you're
not in it. That's right.
>> I think we have to fix the quote.
>> It's a little club
>> and you're not in it.
>> We didn't even realize this little club
existed within the big club. H
>> I think that is fair.
>> Yeah,
>> I tried a psychoactive mushroom
recently. You've heard me talk about it
before. It's not the one everyone always
talks about though. The mushroom I'm
referring to is ammonita muscaria. Red
one with the white spots that you've
seen in folklore stories forever. It's
not psilocybin and it's not a
traditional psychedelic. Although at
high doses, it can be extremely
dissociative and psychoactive in its own
way. For me, it's way more grounding. At
lower doses, it puts you in a calmer,
focused, almost flow state headsp space.
At medium doses, it's more relaxing and
sedating, which is great for sleep and
dreams. Personally, I like Amanita at
lower doses. It makes me calmer and
relaxed, and it's not this crazy like
high feeling or anything like that. The
reason I felt comfortable even trying
Amanita in the first place, though, is
because of Amitara. This entire space is
filled with a bunch of sketchy mushroom
products, and these guys are the
opposite. Clean sourcing, no synthetics,
no fillers, and a huge focus on
education. So, if you'd like to join me
and check out Amitara for yourself, you
can go to www.amantara.com/go/julian.
That link is in my description below.
And use code JD22 at checkout for 22%
off your entire order. Once again,
that's www.antara.com/go/julian.
Link in my description below. And don't
forget to use code JD22 for 22% off your
order. What do you think of what Tucker
said about this revealing perhaps some
sort of super government like su A where
he said the people that you thought were
the highest actually just work for the
people who work for the people that are
the highest.
>> Isn't that the truth? I think he's on to
something.
>> You know, Tucker's another guy who um
has been very deliberate about all this.
He was never one to jump on rumor. He
was always one of the guys who demanded
to see evidence before he took a
position. And I think even he is shocked
by what has been released. And you know
there are a million other little strings
that haven't been pulled yet. Don't
forget there are still reportedly
between three and 3.3 million documents
that have not yet been released.
>> Yes.
>> That Pam Bondi has said won't be
released. She's going to defy a bill
passed 419 to1 in the House and 99 to
nothing in the Senate and signed by the
president and she's just going to say,
"No, I'm not going to do what the bill
commands me to do and release these
documents."
>> Do you think she's saying that or that's
coming from above her?
>> It has to be coming from above her. It
has to be. One of these little strings
that I've been trying to focus on
involves uh Katherryn Remler, who was
the Obama administration's
uh White House counsel.
>> 11,500 emails.
>> First of all, what the [__] right?
Like, does she do nothing all day long
as the White House counsel other than
chitchat with Jeffrey Epstein? Number
one. Number two, there's one there's one
email that she sent him saying, "John
Brennan, the CIA director, gave me the
CIA's highest honor today. Pretty cool,
huh? Or pretty great, huh?" And then she
tries repeatedly to set up a lunch
between Jeffrey Epstein and John
Brennan. Why? To what end? And there's a
bigger question here too and that is
what kind of judgment did these people
exercise? We This woman is supposed to
be the president's personal legal
adviser, his personal attorney,
[clears throat]
>> and and this is what she's doing.
And I I have a theory that I'm confident
about.
Why would she be so close to John
Brennan of all people?
Because every Tuesday morning at 7:00,
John Brennan chaired the kill list
meeting.
And we know that the kill list committee
was chock full of attorneys, White
House, NSC, CIA, DOJ, just to make sure
that yeah, you can legally go out and
just kill these people this week and
then we'll meet up again on Tuesday and
come up with another list of people to
kill. She was on the kill list
committee. I'm confident of it. So,
she's either murdering people or she's
chitchatting with Jeffrey Epstein.
Again, what kind of judgment do these
people have? And then where did she go?
She became the general counsel at
Goldman Sachs.
>> That's right.
>> At least they had the presence of mind
to say, "You got to go."
>> That
>> you can't survive this.
>> I will say this, they should have done
that a few years ago,
>> ages ago when it was when it was first
released that she was in touch with
Jeffrey Epstein. You're absolutely
right.
>> That's right. And like you know there's
just some there there's revelations of
people that had
stronger relationships to the point that
you know they were personally in his
life. [snorts] I want to come back to
Rumbler in a minute because that's a big
story but like Lawrence Krauss I've said
this a million times sat in that chair
>> two years ago got connected to him
through someone else that was on the
podcast. He's a physicist and then when
he was coming in here we knew he had
known Jeffrey Epstein. I asked him about
it on the podcast. He was a nice enough
guy. He's got 7500 emails with Jeffrey
Epstein. So like I'd love to be like,
you know, and and usually like I have a
policy of not really talking against
like people who have been in here and
stuff like that. It's just like a part
of the job. Let other people do that.
But journalistically like you have to do
this. And I I'm not planning on reaching
out to Lawrence to ask him about this or
whatever. But when you are coordinating
with someone that much
>> over all these years and we found out he
was trying to get Jeffrey Epstein on the
Joe Rogan Experience in 2017.
>> Oh my god. You know, it's like,
>> you know, bro, at that point, you know,
and he said in the past, he was quoted
as saying like, you know, well, I only
ever saw Jeffrey around young women who
were 21 or 22, so I assumed that I
believed him, took him at his word when
he said he was
>> funny because that's exactly what Peter
Mandelson said until the picture was
released of him in his underwear with a
16-year-old not realizing that he was
being photographed.
>> That's right. And it's got it's it's got
to be said like when you see there's
other people that are in the emails
where I don't really see anything and
it's only a couple emails and they don't
really seem to like know them well and
I'm like all right it's weird but all
right. But to bring it back to Kathy
now, 11,500.
Very interesting that you put two and
two together with the kill list, which
leads to my question, and again, some of
this has to be theorizing, John. And I
>> sure
>> we weren't [__] there, so we don't
know,
>> right? We don't know. But do you think
that Kathy, before we get to the origins
of Jeffrey Epste and go through all
that, do you think it was that Kathy is
a rising star attorney becoming kind of
like fixer, especially once she got into
the Obama orbit when he gets into
office? Do you think someone like that
was just very clearly a target for
Jeffrey and he then actually possibly
befriended her and then because of the
connections he had, she trusted him and
with information related to things like
I don't know, perhaps a kill list.
>> I think that's likely because if you're
hearing from people like Allan
Dersowitz, what a great guy Jeffrey
Epstein is, right? [laughter]
>> And you know,
>> I know that's your best friend. Yeah,
>> you love him.
>> Yeah, we Yeah, we really love each
other.
Um,
again, what kind of judgment do these
people have? If you're like the most
important constitutional attorney in the
world,
then maybe you should keep your pants on
probably
>> in the presence of a 16-year-old girl.
>> Yeah.
>> You your defense that that your you kept
your underwear on, that's not a defense.
>> [snorts]
>> That's not a defense. You know, I was on
the Pierce Morgan show with him, I don't
know, six, eight months ago,
>> and Pierce called it smackdown
afterwards because I think I rattled
him. I rattled Durowitz. He he said the
most ridiculous thing. I said that I was
confident that Epstein was a was a
Mossad access agent. And I believe that
I've been proven correct. I believe that
I underestimated his contact with
intelligence services. We could talk
about that one.
>> Um, but I'm I'm positive that he was an
Israeli agent of some sort. And
Dersowitz just jumped all over me. And
then he shouted, see this is what he
does. He interrupts to try to knock you
off off balance. But he shouted the most
ridiculous thing. And I laughed at him.
He said that he was Epstein's attorney.
And if Epstein was a spy for the Mossad,
he could have gone to the White House
and he could have gotten him a lighter
sentence. And it's like, I would have
hung him from a tree. [laughter]
>> No, John, I would have hung from a tree.
>> That's right. [laughter] That's right.
Like, you think going to the White House
admitting that your client is spying for
a foreign power
>> Yeah.
>> on you.
>> That's right.
>> That's going to get him leniency. I saw
we can't play it because it actually has
like copyrighted music in the
background, but
>> I was just looking when when right
before you got here, that clip popped up
in my feed of him saying that
>> and it was actually I don't know if you
noticed this cuz you were just on Zoom
like going back and forth, but we can
watch it afterwards and see everything.
>> You could tell as he was getting through
it once he had said CIA or MSAD and then
said I could have gone straight to the
white he went like crap. Oh, whoops.
>> Cats out of the bag.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and you just see Bass
and Musef like
>> He was good. Anyone else get that? You
know what I was like, whoa.
>> But that's a good That's the thing,
John. And I've talked about this a bunch
recently. It's like
>> you're Greek American, right? You're
born You're born here.
>> Born here.
>> Mhm.
>> You're a dual citizen, right?
>> Yes.
>> But you're someone who served the
American government until
>> Oh, I only became a dual citizen in 20
10.
>> That's right. Okay. So, you're even
closer generationally. I'm like fourth
generation or something like that. I'm
half Italian,
>> half Irish.
>> No disrespect to the Irish side. I love
my Irish fans out there.
>> You know, I never identify with the
culture. The food kind of sucks. I go
out of my way to not celebrate St.
Patrick's Day. It kind of is what it is.
It's not a part of my family cultural
history, right?
>> And so, like, if something happened with
Ireland tomorrow, I'd be like, "Wow,
that's really sad, but my life would go
on." On the other hand, the Italian
side, that's my family culture on both
sides that I have lived in the country.
I have family in the country. I love
that place. It's amazing.
>> If tomorrow though, as an Americanborn
Italian, Irish American, if the American
government came to me and said, "Listen,
Jules, some [__] went down last night
and it turns out we are at war with
Italy. Will you before the question
comes out like will you fight for us or
them?" I have on my American fatigues
and AK-47 and I'm taking the nearest
plane, train, or automobile to get the
[__] over to Italy and mow down whatever
Mario and Luigi's get in my way in the
wrong uniform. I'm gonna hate it. I'm
going to hate it, but I'm going to do
it.
>> Yes.
>> And there's a lot of people whose names
ended in a vowel
>> in 1943,
>> whose parents didn't even speak English,
who did the same thing.
>> Did exactly that.
>> And there are many American Jews who
would say the same thing about America.
>> I take issue, it's not about the race. I
take issue with anyone like an Alan
Dersowitz who you know godamn well
American-born dude who's made his whole
life here. You know goddamn well if you
ask him that question you get a blank
stare and he changed the subject and you
know what the answer
>> or even just accuse you of being an
anti-semit.
>> That's right. I couldn't agree with you
more.
>> Mhm. I don't trust him. I don't like
him. Frankly, I don't know anybody that
trusts him.
He's just not the kind of guy that
instills trust.
>> Yeah. And the thing about him that I
have to give him is that ever since the
Epstein story like first came out, he is
one of the only people, if not maybe the
only guy like from that orbit
>> who will get in front of whatever camera
is rolling to discuss the case directly.
I will give him that. I will also give
him that as a attorney he did represent
the guy. He has a job to do there. Yeah.
Whether we like it or not. But David
Boyce was on uh the other he and I were
both on uh Pierce the other day and he
made an important point because David
Boyce is one of the most important
criminal defense attorneys in America
and he said that Dersowitz was more than
just his attorney. He was his friend and
that's fine. You can be friends with
with your clients, even if your clients
are scumbags. But he was Epstein's
publicist
>> and that's not fine.
>> He was
>> for all intents and purposes. Yeah.
>> Interesting.
>> Yeah. Did Did you happen to see Les
Wexner's testimony?
>> I'm glad you brought that up, [laughter]
John.
>> Did Did you catch the hot mic moment?
If you say more than five words, I'm
gonna [__] kill you. [laughter]
>> Yes, I did catch that.
>> I loved it. How about the [__] the re
>> Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah. Boy, Les Wexner,
I I would have so many questions for
Less Wexner. There aren't enough hours
in the day,
>> right? What would What would be the
first thing you'd ask him? What would
possess you to hire a seventh grade
substitute math teacher who had never
finished college to be tax advisor when
you are the richest man in the state of
Ohio? There wasn't one person in the
entire United States of America for you
to hire to advise you on your taxes
than a seventh grade substitute math
teacher who didn't finish college unless
you were also having sex with him.
>> Oh, I didn't see that curveball coming
at the end. That kind of just hit me
like
>> which which he has consistently denied.
He has consider you see his reaction to
that with his face when they did bring
that up in a separate question I might
add. They're like did you ever first of
all he's like leaning forward like this
the whole time and they're like
>> did you ever did you ever have sexual
relations with Jeffrey Epstein he's like
>> I was like I need a body language expert
on that one. I don't know.
>> And you know what he did according to
Vanity Fair as as soon as people started
asking that question he ran out and got
married.
The guy was, you know, well into
adulthood and had never been married.
And then as soon as people started
saying, I wonder if le if Wes Les Wexner
is gay, he ran out and got married.
See, this is what's strange
about that in particular. Not I can't
speak for Less Wexner at all, but on the
other side of the equation, because
these files, to be clear, seem to show
it's girls, boys, children, just in
general,
>> anything went.
>> But on the other side of the equation,
in all the testimony, witnesses,
people who were around Jeffrey Epstein
coming forward, I have never heard
something where it involved a male,
period. It was always young women.
That's right.
>> Or
little girls, right?
>> So, for him to be this would be a, you
know, a a a gay relationship or
encounter like that. And that
I mean, I guess it's totally I guess
nothing's off the table. But it's a
that's always been like a little bit of
a red herring for me. Like I wonder if
it's like Les is doing stuff with people
that Jeffrey's providing
>> and that that could very well have been
it as well. Mhm.
>> So you you asked that question though
about why you'd hire a
>> Yeah.
>> math teacher.
>> Why? And you give him so much money
>> that he ends up
>> power attorney
>> and and power of attorney he ends up
with the widest townhouse in all of
Manhattan.
>> You ever stood outside that place?
>> I went once. Yeah. It's gigantic.
>> Yeah. I give the demented tour of New
York City. People coming into town.
>> That's cool. That would be fun.
>> We stand there. But
>> it's a big place.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> You ever see look at the Google maps and
see how far it goes back?
>> No.
>> Lnick's house is like half the size.
>> Wow.
>> It's nuts. We'll get to let
>> But this was an answer related to the
first half of your question, John. So,
let's let this play right here, De. Why
Les Wexner hired Jeffrey Epstein?
>> Personal work for the Rothschild family
in France. book specifically. I talked
to Ellie De Rothschild and so I
mentioned that earlier. Uh so he he
represented their whole family. There
have been a whole bunch of people many
most of whom I never would have met but
in New LA.
He would say like I'm I'm providing uh
financial advice to the founders of
Google. I'm financial providing
financial advice to Jeff Bezos.
Which to be clear, that was that was
later. That's good. That was later when
he did that. That wasn't from that
answer right there. But
>> it seemed to me when you see the full
there's a full 4minute version of that
as well. That what Wexner was saying,
whether it's true or not is certainly a
question. But what he was saying is that
he was really hitting at the point that
like because he personally talked to
some of the members of the Rothschild
family and they confirmed at the time
this allegedly being
>> in the mid to late 80s something like
that right
>> that they were in fact working with
Jeffrey on whatever basis they were he
>> bonafites. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So first of all do you believe
that or you think there's more there?
>> Oh there's got to be more there. So far
in this entire story, nothing has been
as it seemed.
>> Nothing. There's there's been more
behind all of it, behind every
revelation. And if only half of it's
been released and we're flipping out
over what we've seen so far, what's the
other half include? You know, and why
wasn't it released? Is it even worse
than what we've seen? Is it just a
continuation of what we've seen?
I will say that there are a lot of very
important people out there who have
questions that need to be answered. I
hate that the statute of limitations is
a problem here. I hate
>> Is the statute a problem specifically?
>> A problem in that this stuff can't be
prosecuted.
>> Which stuff?
>> Like child sex crimes.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. There aren't going to be any
charges against anybody. They're going
to be civil suits, but nobody's going to
be charged with a crime. If you look at
even in the UK, the UK has been very
straightforward about all this. They
have Mandelson now and former Prince
Andrew. Andrew was charged with um
with passing a document to Epstein that
had to do with British uh business and
trade negotiations.
>> Alama deal.
>> The Alyama deal. That's exactly right.
And then Mandlesson is rumored to have
given him something from the defense
ministry which could be a violation of
the state the official secrets act. Uh
but none of this stuff has to do with
sex.
>> We'll come back to the alley mama deal
because that has to do with like the
origins here. I just there is so much on
the bone that like it's so hard to stay
on one thing. So I apologize to people
if we jump around a lot but like John
knows everything about this case. So
that'll happen a little bit. But
>> let's stay with Wexner for a minute. So
you'd ask him about the source of
wealth. Then they have a relationship
for at least 20 years. He claims that he
cut him off in 2007. I don't know that I
believe that.
>> Right. [sighs]
>> What else would you ask him? What would
be the burning or to quote Howard
Lutnik, the cutting questions.
>> I mean, I would ask questions that I
know he wouldn't answer truthfully or
honestly. Like I would want rundowns of
every time he went to that island. There
there there's a reason why literally
every room, including the bathrooms,
were wired for audio and video.
>> Mhm.
>> Nobody does that.
>> He said he only went there once on his
boat with his family on the record.
>> Right. I
I I hope that's true. I don't believe
him.
>> I agree. Not if you've been a not just a
friend, but but a a close friend, a best
friend for more than two decades. You
went to the guy's house one time.
>> Come on.
>> It's like Deaf was saying with Howard
Letic's answer at Congress where he's
like, "I went to the island. It was only
for an hour and I left with my wife, my
children, and our nannies."
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz people fly all the way
to the Caribbean for 1 hour.
>> He's like, "You couldn't say def's like
you couldn't say you were there for the
afternoon." Exactly. I mean, it's a
[__] island.
>> Exactly.
>> You know,
>> and that was after Lutnik denied that
they were close friends.
>> Mhm.
>> That [clears throat] that one
>> look at the look at Sarah Ferguson now.
She's in a whole heap of trouble.
>> That's Prince Andrew's ex-wife.
>> Mhm. Well, we knew for a long time that
Jeffrey was like floating her money cuz
they were in debt up to their eyeballs.
Right.
>> I have a good friend who represented her
uh as as one of her attorneys and he
said she was always broke. Always broke.
I don't know where the money went. How
can you be a member of the British royal
family and be broke? I have no idea.
>> That whole thing's sketchy.
>> I mean, specifically targeting that,
too.
>> And then after he's convicted
in 2007
and she says publicly that she's cut him
off, then she emails him, "I'm so sorry,
Jeffrey. I love you. You're the big
brother I never had." And then she takes
her daughters down there to visit him
and then lies about it. Like what kind
of hold did he have on people? I don't
understand this. [snorts]
Do you think I I don't think this for a
second, but I have to ask this just so
you can at least respond. Do you think
some of these people
might have actually believed him at his
word that he's like, "Yeah, I
accidentally ordered a 17year-old. I
thought thought you was 21." Do you
think it's even possible that they would
have believed it?
>> I think it's possible that they wanted
to believe it and then allowed
themselves to believe it.
>> Deep down, no. Unless you're deaf, dumb,
and blind.
>> Yep.
>> Uh I can't imagine. No. Plus, you know,
it's not like people don't talk. I mean,
even Trump said back in the day, Jeffrey
likes him young. Too young for my taste.
>> Yeah. Mhm. A lot of people said there's
there's even emails, I'm trying to
remember who it was with, maybe it was
actually with Mandlesson, but don't
quote me on that, where they're going
back and forth and Jeffrey says,
"Take a picture of of you and and send
me a picture of you and the little girl
or something like that." And the guy
goes like, "Haha, yeah, sure."
[sighs]
Yeah. Yeah. I I interviewed a member of
the British Parliament a couple days ago
for my my own podcast and um and he said
this is enough to bring down the British
government.
>> Yep.
>> Yeah. Like judgment. What kind of
judgment do you people have? And look,
Mandlesen has always been a scumbag,
right? Everybody knew he was a crook. He
had been credibly accused of, you know,
embezzlement and extortion. He's he's
just a crook. they're out there in
politics. And so when word surfaced that
he was close to Jeffrey Epstein and you
know he he had already had to be removed
as business minister and from another
couple of u senior positions in the in
the British Labor Party. He swore to
Kier Starmer the now the prime minister
of the UK. He swore to him that he
barely knew Epstein. They had met once
or twice. There was nothing to these
rumors. And then the emails are
released, including the photo of him
with a 16-year-old girl standing in his
underwear. They're both looking at a
laptop, so it's clear he does not
realize he's being photographed.
And um and then he had to admit that,
okay, all right, you caught me. So he's
resigned from the House of Lords. He's
been thrown out of the Labor Party.
But people aren't just angry at
Mandelen.
And also he was recalled as the British
ambassador to the United States. He's no
longer the ambassador. They're not angry
just at Mandlesen. They're angry at the
prime minister because what kind of
judgment do you have when everybody in
the country knew this guy was a scumbag,
but because he looked you in the eye and
he smiled at you and said, "Oh, no, no,
prime minister. It's not true. None of
it's true." And then your reaction is,
"Okay, I'm going to make you ambassador
to the United States of America."
What goes through their minds?
So this Kierst Starmer may not last as
long as Liz Truss's head of cabbage.
[laughter] This is This is bad.
Already see the meme on that one.
[laughter]
>> Yeah. So, you're also tying into
directly what Ro Kana said as well. And
one thing I like about Massie and Roana
is their delivery is the same with the
exception of I've never seen Massie get
worked up like he did at Pam Bondi. And
I
>> he rarely gets worked up.
>> But he genuinely dislikes Pam Bond.
>> Oh yeah, she's a liar.
>> But Roana will just like these two guys,
Massie and Roana, will just like deliver
this line about the Epstein files. It's
like, wait, I'm sorry. What the [__] did
you just say? And it's like, yeah, so uh
we found this and there it is. All
right, have a good one. They walk out.
So Ro kind of comes out maybe like two 3
weeks ago and he had just walked out of
the DOJ where they he got to see some of
the stuff that they haven't released.
And he was like, "Yeah, so the files
show that this poses an existential risk
for the entire monarchy system in the UK
and then therefore across Europe because
they're all [__] related."
>> Yes.
>> Literally.
>> Which, you know, John, I obviously we
kind of fought a war about that here
like 250 years ago. I'm not a huge fan
of monarchies. I wouldn't shed a tear
about it.
>> I put a laughing emoji every time the
crown prince of Greece posts something
on Facebook.
>> I like that. Yeah. Crown Prince of
Greece. You're not even Greek. You're
Danish. [snorts] How dare you. Shut up,
[laughter] Malaka. Get out of here. I
like that. You got to I'll retweet that
when you do it. Let me know [laughter]
when you do it.
>> But it's like the other problem with
this, and maybe I'm like overthinking
this a little bit,
>> but these systems are so entrenched.
Yes. where from a backdoor economics
perspective, whether it be real estate
holdings, financial holdings, uh,
funnels of money, things like that, if
it all came down at once.
>> It could crash the whole system.
>> Yes,
>> that's real.
>> I think it's real.
>> Yeah. Um, I was watching BBC this
morning, as a matter of fact, and they
said as recently as three years ago, 80%
of the British people support the
monarchy. Today, 50% of the British
people support the monarchy.
>> This is they're at a tipping point. And
if the Brits go, everybody else is going
to go, too. Look at Norway. Who ever
even heard of the Norwegian royal
family? But now you got ties to Epstein.
You got the crown prince's or crown
princess's soning two women. Now he's
got to go on trial. What kind of people
are these? Like, is it really worth it
to to prop up these phonies as your as
your monarchs?
>> No, I don't think so.
>> Of course, it's that's not the question
here. That's not the question. It's like
like if I were just responding with my
anger, I'd want the entire system, we're
not just talking monarchies, to just
[__] get a reset button. That's
right.
>> Right.
>> But I [snorts] also know how much that
would affect all of us if it all
happened all at once. And so that's the
strange dance in trying to go through
this case. How do you find a way to go
in with the raid, right,
>> and hit all the cockroaches,
>> right?
>> But not, you know, accidentally sprayed
in grandma's mouth at the same time.
>> And and this is where you run into that
problem of statutes of limitations
again.
>> Because it would be far easier if you
could just prosecute these people,
right? and and show the people of every
one of these countries involved that it
doesn't matter how famous you are or how
important you are, we're all equal under
the law. And that's just not going to be
the case here.
>> All these famous rich people, they're
all going to get away with it.
[clears throat]
>> It's sick.
>> You don't think anyone in the US will go
to prison for this?
>> I don't. You know, I was talking to an a
constitutional attorney about this and
he said the only way that this that a
prosecution could go forward is if the
Justice Department could successfully
argue
that the cover up of the original crime
continued and constituted a conspiracy.
So, you couldn't be you couldn't be
prosecuted necessarily for the crime
itself. you would be prosecuted for
conspiracy to commit the crime.
But he said even that is a stretch. What
if with statutes of limitations though?
What about all the stuff we're seeing
like in this latest trunch where these
things are occurring a lot of it between
2011 and 2019? I would think there's not
as if if if you were
>> doing cannibal acts on kids in 2015 like
we would be able to prosecute that
>> in some cases on the on the sex cases
the statute is 5 years
>> and so we've missed it
>> which you know what may have been a part
of the plan why didn't Joe [__] Biden
release all this information
>> thank you every administration I would
argue since Clinton has covered this up
and that's the thing absolutely yes
right you have Trump in office right now
and there's a massive cover up happening
and it should be called out. We will
call it out. It is what it is. We'll
talk about that more. But every
administration RD red and blue has had a
chance to put this out. So all these
Democrats who are suddenly just jumping
on the train here because they can,
right? And they can read a question
their intern gave them that's an easy
slam dunk because they covered this up.
It's like I have no energy for those
people either. This is this is a
systemic problem that has happened to
where you're just at a point now where
the Democrats are like, "Well, the
Clintons are so far past time and
they're so old and you know, like we now
we can throw them under the bus. They
ain't like that no more.
>> Nobody cares anymore,
>> right?"
>> Uhhuh.
>> But what about the victims then?
>> What they how does that benefit the
victims in any way? And why why you
finally get to depose Les Waxner, which
how about the fact he was listed as a
co-conspirator in the documents?
>> See, we never knew that.
>> And he's never been interviewed.
>> Never. Like, where was the FBI all these
years? And another thing, too, and this
this goes back to the very basis of this
case,
[snorts]
Epstein got a sweetheart deal in 2006,
right? and the US attorney for the the
uh whatever it was the southern district
the central district of Florida whatever
it was I guess it was the central
district um has said this is Aosta who
became labor secretary in Trump's first
term said that he was ordered to give
this this sweetheart deal okay so where
do orders come who who's the only person
in in the in the system there
who can order a US attorney to do
something. That's the attorney general.
Well, the attorney general was Alberto
Gonzalez who didn't brush his hair in
the morning without permission from the
president or the vice president, right?
He was like legendary for his
powerlessness and ill suiting for the uh
for the position. So,
was it Bush? Was it Cheney?
Who was it that was close enough to
Epstein that he would want to swoop in
and save Epstein by giving him this
sweetheart deal? Nobody has ever
answered that question. And Aosta
apparently genuinely doesn't know the
answer. His order came down from the
attorney general.
>> I think I believe him on that.
>> I do too. I believe him
>> cuz he said he I was told he belonged to
intelligence.
>> Intelligence. That's the line.
>> That was the word. He belonged to
intelligence.
Well, this gets into that super
government
>> kind of thing cuz it's like
you say Bush and Cheney, which makes a
lot of sense to me, but now like my
whole worldview is just like,
>> oh yeah, it's ridiculous. You know, I
used to I used to just piss all over
people's analysis when they would start
talking about the trilateral commission
[laughter] and Bilderberg and the
Shangrila conference and then somebody
to whom I used to be very close
>> used to used to and about whom a court
order exists saying I cannot talk about
her um in any public forum.
She went to one of those events.
She was invited because she rose up high
enough in the corporate structure that
she went. And I I couldn't wait to hear
what was it like. And she said, "It's a
lot of really rich, really important
people
talking about arms deals."
>> Arms deals.
>> It was all about arms deals. And she
said, "Except for except for Davos." She
went to Davos and she said, "That's
where they were all talking about how to
manage the global economy."
And I said, "So, so all that shit's true
that they're the ones that sort of set
the policy?" And she said, "Yeah, I saw
it with my own eyes.
I
>> but I'm I'm not
>> Can you get me a pen
>> allowed to identify who that person is
nor it's on it's on the counter out
there.
>> Usually I I've never needed that before
but I I may need that today after after
hearing that. All right. So the
trilateral commission for people out
there who are unfamiliar. This is
something that's been written about a
lot in the past and once again it's
something that's always written off like
oh god this is where
>> another conspiracy theory well
>> but it's not go so fast
>> it's all it's a real thing
>> it is they even have a website
>> they have a website
>> we pull up the trilateral commission
[laughter]
>> and and Bilderberg they list all the
people that attend this but by name all
these people and you'll recognize 80% of
Oh man.
>> Well, I mean, I guess that's hiding in
plain sight, but it's something where I
I guess what I should say is the
connotation of it was where the
conspiracy theorists would be saying
something and people would be like, "No,
it's just this group. It's the It's
David Rockefeller." Like,
>> I know, right?
>> Arand Rothschild, you know? And yeah,
listen, they we put Clinton on it. He
was he was bored after he left office,
you know. And then you get Epstein in
this this sit down with Steve Bannon. We
we will talk about him, but you get
Epstein saying, "Yeah, I was on the uh
trilateral commission and here's how I
got." And he makes it sound so simple.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> I'm like, "How do you even get there,
buddy? You're a kid from Coney Island."
>> Yeah. Somebody taps you on the shoulder.
Next thing you know, you're getting an
email.
>> Dave, can you put the camera on, John?
>> Yeah. I I see what you're reading.
>> Son of a [__]
Really?
I knew it. But really?
>> Yeah. It was very
>> How she get in there? God damn it.
>> It was very disappointing to me.
[laughter]
>> You can't talk about that by court
order.
>> No, sir.
>> Yeah.
I already didn't like her. Now I really
don't like her. But wow. Wow.
>> Yeah. This is the life I've given
myself. And I'm just Yeah. [laughter]
myself. [laughter]
>> Okay. So,
back to the Oh, wait. Sweetheart deal
because we were talking about where that
would come from. You know, I'm trying to
not let my brain run too wild with now
every possible answer is all over here
and it's all like absolutely the worst
thing ever. But clearly some of the
answers are there. So
>> without getting to his origin story yet
because that's again we're going to do
that. But you talk about at the
trilateral commission they are going
over arms deals and everything and now
this is entering your world of things
that you have witnessed around the world
and how [__] works. What is it about
arms deals that would make it the number
one priority for the quote unquote
Illuminati of the world
>> of of the Pentagon's $1 trillion budget
fully a third goes to weapons and
weapons systems right that's just for us
>> so couple that with what we're able to
sell to other countries whose leaders
are at these conferences I mean that
we're talking about you know probably a
majority of the American economy year
after year after year.
It's how we employ Americans.
>> [snorts]
>> I read something recently. Oh, the
Washington Post, the New York Times,
that the Pentagon has assiduously placed
manufacturers,
or I shouldn't say placed manufacturers,
they have placed orders with
manufacturers
in literally every one of the 435
congressional districts. So literally
every single member of Congress has
constituents who are dependent on the
defense economy,
on the defense budget.
And so there's no incentive for any
member of Congress to vote no on DoD
>> and also paid by all those companies.
>> Yeah, sure. I mean, it costs what, five,
eight, 10, 20 million dollars to run for
Congress. Every two years, that money's
got to come from somewhere. So, it comes
from Defense Department packs.
>> They buy them off on the micro and then
it wins them the macro when you put the
numbers together. Yeah. Def, what' you
pull up here?
>> Just confirm.
>> All right. So, the Washington Post
reports that the Pentagon structurally
distributes manufacturing and
contracting across almost every
congressional district to secure broad
local political support, making budget
cuts difficult. The strategy embeds
defense spending into the local economy
with analysis showing that despite a
high concentration of funds among top
contractors, the broader supply chain is
deeply embedded in domestic districts.
>> Yeah.
>> A friend of mine um has a little kind of
little mom and pop manufacturing plant
in Beaver County, Pennsylvania.
>> Aritine International.
>> No, no, no. It's a little
just a little place you've never heard
of.
>> Got it. And he mentioned something to me
one time. Oh, this is probably five
years ago. He mentioned that he is
entirely dependent on the Pentagon. And
I was like, "The Pentagon?" I said, "For
what?" Oh, I can't tell you. He said,
"It's a classified program." I said,
"Seriously, George?" Like, I thought he
was making, you know, heels for shoes or
something. I didn't know what he was
making. [laughter] And then later on he
told me like, "No, it's this little
widget that fits inside, you know, the
the motor for a, you know, Patriot
missile or something like that."
>> Nice.
>> And he's like, "In in Beaver County."
And he's like, "Yeah." And then when I
saw that report in the Washington Post,
I was like, "Oh, of course it all makes
sense." H
what percentage of the trilateral
commission if you had to broadly guess
do you think is influenced by bankers
around the world?
>> Oh all of it.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Sure.
>> The reason I asked that is because again
I I love this supra term that Tucker
came up with because I think it's great
visual. Right. So presidents of the
power countries around the world, the
ones that actually matter at the UN,
right? So think like US, China, Russia.
>> And then you know the people below them
too. But
>> above that you got let's say the fixer
class like the Epsteines of the world
who really hold the power to pull the
strings on the peasante right here who
are the presidents and kings and all
that [__]
>> And then above that you have the people
who finance them. and the people who
finance them as bankers.
If you want to look at this this way,
and it's fair to do it right now, look
at things like financing wars to make
money and profit off death, which also
we could even get into the conversation
of them trying to manage population
control and doing so. Is that a
ridiculous statement?
>> I think that's a conversation that ought
to be out there. Yeah. For the
>> What makes you think we should have that
conversation? Like what kinds of things
that you've heard? population control
and even the reverse of that is
something that is now making headlines.
I read an article just in the past week
or two that China likely does not have
1.1 billion people, that they've
consistently lied about their population
and that they probably have something
closer to 650 million or 700 million
people, but they want the rest of the
world to believe that they have all
these people because it makes it makes
the case for these strong economic
numbers that they're always putting out,
which also are probably not true.
[clears throat]
Um, a country like Greece,
Greece is in trouble because Greece went
through this very long-term economic um,
it was a depression. It wasn't even a
recession. It was a depression. And so
much of the educated middle class,
doctors, lawyers, engineers,
businessmen, they just left. They went
to the US, the UK, Australia, Canada,
Germany. And so there almost is no
middle class or no upper middle class in
Greece. it just left. Well, the economy
then is unsustainable because there's
nobody there to create jobs. There was a
there was a piece oh years ago um in the
Washington Post saying if you look at
the shrinkage in Russia's population,
if it keeps declining at its current
rate, you're going to like this. In 150
years, there won't be any Russians. They
just won't exist anymore. What's the
State Department going to do that thing
to call out? Then what do you do? Now,
of course, immigration changes that that
calculus, but you know, we're talking
about the the possible
um
what's what's the word? Uh the
possibility that countries just can no
longer remain viable as countries
without real population changes. I told
you about my encounter with David
Rockefeller, did I not? You did not tell
me about that.
>> No.
>> I was I was working in Bahrain in the
American embassy. I was the economic
officer and I was a longtime subscriber
to this wonderful magazine called Art
News Magazine. And I read this article
about David Rockefeller being given this
major like art world award for the work
that he's done over the course of, you
know, 75 years or whatever it was for
art in New York. And then we get a cable
from the state department saying that
David Rockefeller is coming to Bahrain
because he's being given an award by the
Bahraini American Bankers Association
and the ambassador comes into my office,
David Ransom, wonderful, wonderful
ambassador, lovely human being, one of
the best bosses I ever had. And he said,
"Hey, uh, we got a cable from from state
saying that David Rockefeller is coming
out to Bahrain. He's going to collect
this award from the bankers association.
I said, "The banker's association?" And
he said, "Yeah, I want you to be his
control officer." I said, "I'd love to
be his control officer." What that means
is you arrange the car, you arrange the
the hotel, you make sure he gets from
point A to point B and just make sure
there are no problems. If he wants to go
shopping, you take him shopping, you do
anything he wants. I welcomed it. Well,
as soon as the Bahrainis heard that
David Rockefeller was coming, his
highness the Aamir announces we're going
to do a state dinner, right? So, the
entire cabinet, the entire royal family,
the entire diplomatic corps, all the
ambassadors, all the credited diplomats,
this is a major event, like the biggest
social event of the year. It's it's at
his main palace. There like 500 people
there. So I go and I was saving my
congrat See, I thought I was very
clever. I was just a stupid kid. So I I
saved my my congratulations for his
award for the receiving line. So I said
to the amir, it's such a pleasure to see
you, your highness. And I said to the
prime minister, we didn't like each
other very much. Like you know, hello.
[laughter]
>> Hello.
>> Hello. He would always say hello
Kiryaku. [laughter]
Yeah. And then he would kind of stare at
me.
>> You're like the spy version of a VEP
episode. I don't know if anyone ever
told you that, but
>> And then it comes David Rockefeller and
I said, "Mr. Rockefeller, I wanted to
congratulate you on your, you know,
whatever it was called award." Oh, he
lights up. Thank you so much. I'm so
proud of that award, the Guggenheim and
the madness. And then I, you know, go
and then the next night he collects his
award from the bankers association and
he leaves. So we had a 9:00 meeting in
the embassy every day. It was, you know,
the ambassador, the deputy chief of
mission and and the heads of all the
departments. So I'm in there in the
morning meeting and the ambassador says,
"So the Rockefeller visit went very
well." And I said, cuz I'm an idiot, I
said, "Why would a guy who's almost a
hundred years old fly halfway around the
world to collect a little trophy from
some bankers that he's never met
before?" [laughter]
And the ambassador goes like this. He
goes, "John, John, [laughter]
you're supposed to be the smart one." He
says,
[laughter]
I said, "What? What am I missing?" He's
like, "He didn't come for the banker's
award.
That was his cover stuff." [laughter]
And I said, "So what was he doing here?"
He said, "David Rockefeller is the
secret back channel to Saddam Hussein.
He came here to make it look like he had
business in the Middle East. We put him
on a military transport this morning and
sent him to Baghdad to tell Saddam
Hussein to cut it out or you're going to
get a bomb up your ass." And then he
flew back from Baghdad. And I was like,
man, I I have a lot to learn.
Wow.
That that didn't impact your worldview a
little bit.
>> Oh yeah, it sure did. [laughter]
>> Like things are not what they seem.
>> Might be an inappropriate thing to say
these days, but that's like a Jay-Z
line.
>> We got Rockefeller out there with
Saddam.
>> Yeah,
>> yeah, that's uh
>> I'm friendly with his daughter now and
she uh
>> Rockefeller.
>> Yeah, Abby Rockefeller. She's very very
sweet. No, no, no. She's a communist and
uh yeah, Aby's great. She she went to
Harvard in the 60s and became a
communist and rebelled against her
family and she gives all of her money to
leftwing
>> Oh my god.
>> charities and and [snorts] concerns.
She's fantastic.
>> That's too good. [laughter]
>> Keep going. I'm sorry.
>> No, I I mentioned the story to her and
she said, "Yeah, that sounds exactly
like something my dad would do." Yeah.
[snorts]
What do I know?
>> Yeah. I guess. Well, she went the
opposite way. Give her that, I guess.
But how'd you become friends with her?
>> I'm on the board of Covert Action
Magazine and uh and she's a supporter of
the magazine.
>> No kidding. That's not Covert Action
Magazine. That doesn't sound sketchy at
all.
>> It was founded by Philip Agy
>> who uh the CIA tried to assassinate for
decades. He was a CIA case officer who
saw what covert actions were were doing
to innocent people in Latin America in
the late60s. And so he went public and
wrote a book called Inside the Company.
And as an appendix
at the back of the book, he listed the
names of every CIA officer he ever
encountered and outed everybody
and then took off for Cuba.
And uh the CIA hunted him down from
country to country to country. They
finally gave up. He died in Cuba. I
don't know 10 years ago, 20 years ago.
And um his son has kept the magazine
going. And and the co-founder of the
magazine, Lou Wolf. Shout out to Lou,
who's now like 87 or 88 years old. He's
a good friend of mine. Um this was Lou's
baby with Philip Ag. And uh and the
magazine still it's still a monthly
concern. I write for it every month.
Do you think [clears throat] we have so
many examples of where covert actions
were just taken for like imperialism
purposes or just because we felt like
overthrowing?
>> There's actually a Wikipedia page.
>> Let's pull it up.
>> Yeah. CIA covert action. Wikipedia. The
first one was the uh 1949
Italian election,
>> right? with the communists. And there
was a deleted scene in The Godfather
that Francis Copela put in there where
Michael's walking in the fields with
Fabitio. Yeah. and he sees in the in the
hillsides at Corleó
>> and he sees the the red like little army
of you know communist supporters right
there and he's like
whatever and Fabrito is like
>> and that was right around the it's
taking place right around the time where
that was going to be a thing where they
were going to come in and take over the
power vacuum post Mussolini with the
opposite side and then CIA is like
>> no no you don't that that covered action
operation. It was the first one and it's
been declassified by the CIA. Um, it was
very simple. They gave $150,000 in cash
to the Christian Democratic Party, which
was the Conservative Party. It was
behind the Communists in the polls.
>> They were going to lose the election.
The Communists were going to win. You
can't have a Communist government in
Western Europe, right? That's just for
the East Eastern Party of Europe.
>> And so what they did is they used that
money to bribe um journalists to write
pro-onservative articles in the run-up
to the election and they were able to
swing just enough votes that the
conservatives won
>> and it was only 150 grand.
>> Yeah, it was the first one.
>> So
>> that was a lot of money in the 40s
though.
>> I know. But for the whole party for a
bunch of journalists, I mean I'm
splitting up that pie. It's getting
smaller. And you think like Don Calini
was taking a baseball bat to people too?
>> Well, I mean, think of it this way, too.
If you're a journalist and you're asked
to write 500 words, that's probably
worth $500 in 1949 money. I mean, if
that's what you get paid today, that was
a lot of money in 194.
>> Yeah. But if I'm going to swing an
election, you got to add a zero to that.
[laughter]
>> Yeah, maybe.
>> Yeah. So, you you're [laughter]
>> All right. So, we're looking at this
Wikipedia page. Everyone else can pull
this up, too. And it's funny because
Wikipedia is run by the CIA, and they
can't even stop this article from
happening. Well, oftentimes the CIA gets
outed. Um, when people look at the um at
the ISP information for the editors, it
oftentimes goes back to Langley.
>> They're that dumb. Come on.
>> Yeah. They're that dumb. Really? Yeah.
Yeah. I remember in my own case, we we
asked um
we asked for something in Discovery. I
don't remember what it was. And it was
we were we were having a meeting, all
the attorneys, I had 11 attorneys. And
um one of them said, "Hey, we should ask
for X." And uh one of the other
attorneys said, "Oh, come on. They're
not that stupid." And he said, "No,
actually they are that stupid." And sure
enough,
they had [__] it up. [laughter] And um
and they ended up having to drop three
charges
>> just because of that.
>> Huh?
>> They're arrogant.
>> Yeah. They think they're smarter than
everybody else is, that they don't make
mistakes, or even if they do make
mistakes, you're not smart enough to
figure out that they've made a mistake.
And that's just simply not true.
>> But it's also like John, they have a VC
arm, as we've outlined before, everyone
outlines it inel
>> and they admit who they invest. Oh yeah,
we threw money in Palanteer in. And now
look at Palanteer, billions in revenue.
>> And it's like, that's where sometimes I
wonder.
Yes, I hear you. There's hubris there.
There's [__] you. We can do what we
want. We're seeing that play out on a
massive scale right now. But sometimes I
wonder if there's
>> if I'm crazy to wonder it too, if
there's like a 5D chess thing here where
people are like, we know some of this
[__] will come out and that's what we
want to happen because we want society
to flip the [__] out.
>> Sure. That happens. That that happens
sometimes.
>> Yeah. And it could have happened with
things that not even related to your
case, but that CIA might do as it
relates to Wikipedia where they're like,
"Yeah, people will flip out about this
by 2025 after 2026 after we do that
whole pandemic thing."
>> Right. Exactly.
>> Oh, exactly.
>> I mean, as an example, sure, why not
hypothetically?
>> Hypothetically, sure.
>> Okay.
>> Sure. And another thing too is if you
throw, you know, so many of these ideas
for operations out there or these little
mini operations,
there's some that are just going to, you
know, not come to people's attention.
They're not going to realize that it's a
some sort of a covert action operation
or disinformation operation.
>> A disinformation. See, that's the big
one now today.
>> You don't know who's behind keyboards
anywhere, right? We do it to a ton of
people.
>> You don't. Even even the people who are
supposed to be the good guys, you can't
trust. I've told you this before. I've
got this buddy, Jason Leupold. He's at
Bloomberg. Jason is one of the best
investigative journalists I've ever
encountered in my life. And honest
honest as the day is long, he um he's
the foyer king. He's filed more Freedom
of Information Act requests than anybody
else in the history of the Freedom of
Information Act. To the point where
George W. Bush's Pentagon spokesman
called him a foyer terrorist on the
record. Called him a foyer terrorist. It
was Jason that broke the Hillary Clinton
email uh scandal.
>> Whoa. I didn't know that.
>> Through a foyer request.
>> He got that through a foy. That's it.
>> So he told me, this is about 10 years
ago. He told me that he was bored one
one week over Christmas break. He was
bored. So he just filed a foyer request.
He had nothing else to do.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> And he asks for
all communications between the CIA and
all journalists. Period.
>> Anything
>> for for this period? No. No. For this
this period of whatever it was, a year I
think is what it was.
>> And you know the CIA never ever ever
answers foyas. They say, "Oh, they send
you a letter saying, "Okay, thank you.
It's it's in Q." Well, I filed a foyer
request 15 years ago. I'm still waiting.
>> What's the legality of that, though?
>> They have 60 days. So, what happens is
when day 60 comes, you have to sue them.
And you will always win.
And because the law is clear, they have
60 days. You will always win. And the
judge will always make them pay your
legal fees
>> because you because you won.
>> But
Uh-uh. He wins every single time.
>> So, they do give it to him.
>> Yeah, they have to.
>> Why haven't you gotten yours? It's been
>> because I haven't sued them.
>> I don't I don't care anymore.
>> I I I wanted to write an article about
>> start a GoFundMe so John can sue these
guys. I I wanted to write an article
about um a guy who I I think was
probably a CIA officer in the early 50s
and he became a um science fiction
author and then he had a mental
breakdown and committed suicide and I
think he was one of the MK Ultra
victims.
>> Do you want to say who this is or
>> you know what to tell you the honest to
God's truth I don't remember his name
anymore. It's been so many years. I'm
sure I still have the foyer request. The
way that started, I was worried you were
gonna say Elron Hover.
>> No name for like, oh [__]
>> no. I don't want to poke that hornets
nest. I have enough problems in my life.
[laughter] Thank you. And take on the
Church of Scientology.
[laughter]
>> No way. So anyway, um he files this
foyer request at Christmas. This is like
Christmas of 2015
maybe.
And
they don't respond. So he sues them. He
used the same attorney every time,
Jeffrey Light, who's now retired,
Jeffrey never ever ever lost a foyer
case. And so finally, they just give him
this dump and he found several things
that were fascinating. One, Kendallian,
formerly of the Los Angeles Times, now
the chief intelligence correspondent,
chief national security correspondent
for NBC News and MS Now. Okay. He was
writing articles and then sending them
to the C to the CIA for clearance before
he sent them to his own editors.
Is it okay, guys, if I write this about
you? Because if it's not okay, just tell
me and I'll I'll kill it.
>> Oh, no.
>> Yeah. Number one, scandalous. He should
have resigned.
>> Yeah. Number two,
um
there was this young, unknown, hungry
independent journalist who actually
stumbled on a story and he's like, "Hey,
I found this information and I'm writing
this article. It's going to go out
tomorrow. Would you care to comment?"
And they wrote back to him and they
said, "So help us God. If you publish
this, you will never be invited to the
Christmas party ever again, and we will
never give you an off therecord
briefing. You're going to be banned.
>> Oh, and he killed his own article. You
know, people say all the time, "Oh,
Operation, you know, Grasshopper,
whatever it was called, uh, paper, not
paperclip. What was the one that where
they were recruiting journalists?"
Operation
>> Oh my god.
>> Whatever.
>> Not Midnight Climax. No, that that was
part of MK Ultra.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Chick looked that up. Beef Mark Gagna
and I talked about that in September
2024 on his show. I remember that, but I
can't remember the name.
>> Mockingbird. Thank you. Operation
Mockingbird. People are like, "Well, you
know, Operation Mockingbird." They don't
need Operation Mockingbird anymore.
>> They just threaten you and and tell you
you're not invited to the Christmas
party. They don't need to recruit people
anymore.
>> It's access journalism.
>> That's exactly what it is. And it's it's
a result of the demise of investigative
journalism. Very very few outlets
anywhere in America have budgets for
investigative journalism anymore. I have
I can't say that I've had people like
from intelligence or something call up
and try to get you to do stuff. But I've
had some weird calls from normal people
with normal jobs, you know, let's say in
like middleman type things where they're
trying to anchor you to ideas and
stories and certain people and stuff
like that. I've dealt with it a lot and
it to me immediately blinks off as like
audience capture,
>> right? And almost all the time, these
are things that
if I did it, not every time, but a lot
of the times, if I did it, we'd make a
lot of money.
>> Yeah.
>> A lot of money. There was I I won't say
what it was, but there were backtoback
days
>> a couple months ago where I was offered
whale and whale.
>> These are episodes that would do they
would pay my bills for seven, eight
months. And I could not have said no
fast enough.
>> Good for you.
>> Because I know algorithmically what it
would also do.
>> And that's what they do. They want to
get people they whoever the [__] they
are cuz it's someone who's below
>> and you'll never figure it out who they
are.
>> They want to influence people to get
just certain things in the algorithm at
all times so that their income becomes
tethered to that. And that's a really
dangerous thing. I've said to people
before,
I know I knew the system probably enough
by March or April 2022
>> that I won't get into details, but if I
wanted to have eight or nine million
subscribers today, I could have done it.
>> I have 1.13,
>> which is also incredible.
>> Thank you.
I would love to be able to have more
money to put into this though and really
be able to build it out and I can't do
that. But I've kept my principles intact
in doing that because to get to that
eight or nine, you are selling your
soul. There is absolutely no middle
ground. There is no gray area. I know
exactly what it was and it's like do it
or don't, but that's an easy call for
me.
>> Yeah, I have to agree with you. If you
don't have your self-respect and
independence,
then what do you have?
>> Yeah. Now, there's another side to what
you're saying though about the
journalist though that gets really
weird. And a mutual friend of ours, Joby
Warick, has talked about this openly.
>> And Joby Job's like the guiding light on
this issue. Yeah.
>> And he's very diplomatic.
>> One of the most diplomatic people I've
ever met in my life. So Job's been the
national security reporter
>> forever
>> forever at the Washington Post. He's got
two Pulitzers
>> and
>> and and he's an incredible author. Like
his books just rocket straight to number
one on the New York Times bestsellers
list and they're incredibly researched.
>> They're so well done. But love the guy
and the very first time I ever talked
with him on episode 134, he he was going
through it and then talked about it with
me off camera. He said, "There's a
really tough thing." He's like, I've got
sources in intelligence that I'm really
good friends with and stuff. And that's
like, then are they telling you the
truth? Are they using the friendship?
But then also, he goes, you'll write a
story and as a journalist, you have to
go to the people involved with the story
and offer a chance to comment before it
gets published. and he'll get a con
he'll get a call from CIA with his
editor in the room right there or NSA or
whoever and say if you publish this X
number of people will die next year.
They always say that, right?
>> And he said, "We legit have to go into a
conference room and basically play like
blind, you know, monkeys throwing darts
at the board to see if this is one of
those where they're lying or not."
>> It's absolutely true. Yes. And if it's
really really sensitive, you'll get a
call from the national security adviser
above the CIA director.
>> Shouldn't that set off a lot of alarm
bells though?
>> Definitely.
What is the line there? Like if you
let's say there is one and for real
150 people, whoever they are, are going
to die from it. But
>> there's no easy answer. I I will say
though that
they they throw that whole blood on your
hands argument at people all the time.
Tom Drake tells this fantastic story.
Tom Drake, the NSA whistleblower. Um Tom
Tom is the one who who first told us
that NSA was spying on Americans after
911. They were just waiting for 9/11 to
happen so that they could spy on
Americans, which is what they did and
they continued to do 25 years later. So
Tom was charged with nine felonies,
including seven counts of espionage and
two counts of theft of government
property, which was the information. He
walked out of the building with the
information in his head and they charged
him with theft.
>> Thought crime.
>> Yeah. So to make a long story short, the
entire case fell apart and all of the
charges were thrown out. But he went to
a profer meeting at the Justice
Department where they say, "Here's the
information we have against you, and
here's the sentence we're going to ask
for when we convict you, unless you want
to confess. Tell us some answers to
questions we may have, and then we can
talk about a slightly lighter sentence."
So, he was looking at it was like 55
years. It was I think it was 55 years.
It was a long time.
And um
and they said, "You have the blood of
dozens of American soldiers on your
hands." And to his credit, he says,
"Name one,
one single soldier who died because I
said NSA was spying on Americans. Name
one and I'll take a guilty plea. Name
him." And then they backed off. And then
later on after the the case was thrown
out,
um they left
the accusations against him on the NSA
and the DOJ websites, but they took out
the slide where they accused him of
having the blood of American soldiers on
his hands. They just make that [__] up
and throw it at you to scare you. They
do it all the time.
>> They even did it with Maduro.
>> Yeah.
>> Who's a bad guy.
>> Yeah, sure. Remember the cartel de loses
that that got removed from the
indictment the minute he touched down
over here on 30th Street
>> never existed.
>> There's I don't I forget the term for it
off the top of my head. Maybe if I
describe it right, you can look it up,
de but like the
h it's like obfuscation by over
stimulation like providing way too much
information that people are like I ain't
reading all that that you can just kind
of like [snorts]
>> poke in little things
documents. Yes, exactly. I love the
transition that you were catching on to
there,
>> John, because as you said correctly,
it's and we should go back to that now
because that's why people are here. But
as you said very correctly, there's
another two and a half to three million
documents. I've heard varying numbers on
that. Correct me in the comments, people
that they have now said we're never
going to release.
And people like Tim Bchett have come out
and said who's seen some of these
documents has come out and said things
like this includes cannibalism.
>> Yeah.
>> And stuff like that. And you have to
wonder
when you think about
let's say a report that Marjorie Taylor
Green has relayed about her conversation
with Donald Trump on this to where he
said this is going to hurt a lot of my
friends if it comes out. You have to
wonder what types of friends are being
protected obviously. And then
furthermore, why the [__] are you
friends with these people? If these are
the things they do cuz to me it's like I
don't want the president to be a
pedophile or associated with that stuff.
[__] I want to believe he's not. But
they fired Joe Pno in two days for
covering up one guy in 2002. The guy had
the [__] stadium named after him at
Penn State. This is the president of the
United States who along again and I will
say this along with every administration
before him. Name them. Clinton, Obama,
Bush, Biden, Trump won, all of them,
they've all covered this up and it's the
most massive pedophilia and many other
things scandal. We we'll talk about the
national security in a minute that we've
ever seen. What does that say about him?
>> A lot. Unfortunately, and I I'll add
something to that, there's an internal
Bureau of Prisons rule at DOJ that
anybody convicted of a child sex crime
is forbidden from serving his or her
sentence in a in a minimum security work
camp.
>> Mhm.
>> Can't do it. They also don't serve their
sentences in maximum security
penitentiies or medium security prisons
because they'll be killed there. Right.
Everybody beats on pedophiles in prison.
So all of the pedophiles go to low
security prisons. So there's still, you
know, the double concertina wire and the
controlled movements and all that stuff.
But in a minimum, you're free to just
come and go as you please. There are no
lock doors. There are no bars in the
windows. Most everybody works in town,
you know, as a janitor or a gardener.
>> Pedophiles are working in town. They're
not supposed to be because there aren't
supposed to be any pedophiles in the
minimum security work camps. But that's
where Galain Maxwell was sent. Minimum
security work. She's the only pedophile
in the entire federal prison system
who's in a minimum security work camp.
And she was transferred there
by the president. Why? Why would he do
something like that?
>> I sent you an article before this,
Steve. There were a few in the text. I
don't know if you can pull it up, but it
was the guy talking about the three
reports
related to Maxwell
and Trump. If you just go through our
text chain, it's somewhere in there. But
what Def will get it in a sec cuz I I
sent D like 15 things right before we
went on. But
you have to wonder.
I mean, this is a lady who's pictured at
the Clinton's daughter's funeral leaning
over the edge. This is a lady who's
pictured with every master of the
universe. This is a lady who's directly
tied to the royal family, whose father
is at the center of this whole thing,
who knew Donald Trump for 30 like they
know she knew everybody. So, what does
she what does she have on him? Like,
maybe here's a good way to start it. Do
you see any scenario where Jeffrey
Epstein as a spy, which he definitely
was a spy, was not
prioritizing blackmail as a means to get
whatever it is he needed to get?
>> He had to have been.
>> I mean, what's the point of running the
operation if it's not to collect
compromat?
You know, one one of the things that I
learned very early on at the CIA was
um we really really didn't like to
squeeze people, right, with you know,
surreptitiously taken photographs of
them with prostitutes or, you know, you
want you want to recruit somebody based
on a a friendly relationship. You want
them to do it because they like you and
they trust you. They're probably doing
it for the money,
>> right?
But you don't want to threaten people.
The Russians do that. The Israelis also
do that. And so from the very beginning,
I thought that this this was a part of
the whole Epstein saga.
>> It was about blackmail. It had to have
been. I don't understand it otherwise. I
don't understand what the draw. First of
all, he's a creepy looking guy.
>> Yeah.
>> He's He's naked half the time
apparently. Mhm.
>> Virginia Ju said he had a deformed penis
that looked like an egg.
>> Mhm.
>> So, what's this guy have going for him
besides [snorts] money? But they all
have money. So, what's the difference?
[laughter]
See, now I want to say something
serious, but making me laugh.
So, I had an Epstein victim sitting in
that chair the other day, and this
part's not funny, but
the thing that really struck me in what
she was saying, and that episode will
come out after this one, by the way,
people, and it'll be two episodes,
was how
brilliant of a manipulator he was.
>> Oh, that's interesting.
>> And that's what he had going for him.
And I'm going to give you an example on
this that she would say he would call
her up cuz she was a model and set an
actress and set her up with meetings in
Hollywood, New York, wherever that he's
not going to be at was someone powerful
that he knew. And the idea is that she's
going to get
>> at these meetings.
>> Oh my god.
>> And she would go to them and most of the
time nothing would happen. But he would
call her after every single one. Now,
when she brought this up an hour
earlier, I had asked her the question.
I'd said, "Do you think that
like we don't know much about Jeffrey
Epstein's childhood? We know he had
parents. We know he had a brother, grew
up in Coney Island, but we don't know
what was going on when Jeffrey Epstein
was 9 years old. So, it's possible he's
a monster that was abused as a child."
>> Certainly possible. Sure.
>> But like, let's assume he wasn't. where
do you think a person like that learns
the psychological tactics to be able to
become this monster to get people? And
she was like, "That's a great question."
And it's like a rhetorical question. I
don't expect anyone to have an answer.
But then an hour later, she's talking
about these phone calls and he would
call her after all of these meetings and
he'd want to know every detail like like
drastically like, "All right, what do
you say? What do you do?" And and he'd
be like, "Did you hook up with her?"
which means that she would have been
raped. And she'd be like, "No." And he'd
be like, "Why not? What? What? When you
went in there, what do you do? What do
you say?" And I said, "Oh my god,
he's like Bill Bichc and Tom Brady
watching football tape except he's
getting tape of [__] predators and
what works and what doesn't."
>> Yes. And so that guy having those types
of skills and like the first time he
came in and met her, he wanted to know
all about her dreams, her family, the
dynamics, what she was interested in
life, places she wanted to go, you know,
all these psychological things that hook
you to someone and make you trust them.
He obviously had those skills. And these
skills would be paramount, correct me if
I'm wrong, in being able to be someone
who wanted to surreptitiously get
information for espionage purposes. Is
that fair to say?
>> Absolutely. Yes.
100%.
Mhm.
So, with the blackmail,
I was talking with someone else on the
phone the other day who I'll probably
have on the podcast to talk about this
and make the arguments, but he was, I
don't know, steelmanning the argument
that the blackmail was defensive
blackmail, paranoia blackmail. And at
the end of his argument, I said to him,
I was like,
"Every leap you had to make to make the
argument that it was just defensive in
in nature, I don't have to make a single
one of those leaps to say it was
offensive in nature."
>> Absolutely right.
Absolutely right.
>> You know, and it's one thing to have a
little kernel of of a story that you
tuck back in your mind just in case you
need it to protect yourself at some
point. It's an entirely different thing
to 24 hours a day collect intelligence
on everybody.
I I'm I just don't buy the argument that
it was defensive in nature. No.
>> Meaning he was doing that
for himself. But the question is, and
now now we should get to the origin
story. Was he doing that at the behest
as a literal employee or as a
>> Well, see, that's really the the $64,000
question. And my thinking has evolved.
Do you know what that's a reference to?
>> I actually don't.
>> Oh, it's a it was a game show in the
1950s called The $64,000 question. It
was like Jeopardy. You get to the end
and if you win the big prize, it's
$64,000. But it went off the air because
it turned out it was fixed. And so the
producers and the hosts were were
prosecuted. [laughter]
>> So it's no it was no longer on TV after
a few years. Anyway,
>> when somebody cuts right to the chase,
that's the $64,000 question.
>> Gotcha.
>> Um
my thinking has changed on this has has
evolved on this. I've always maintained
that Epstein
to me was obviously a Mossad access
agent. And I I said that right here on
the show.
>> Now, with the release of this latest
trunch of documents,
>> I think he was more than that and that
he was probably not exclusive to the
Israelis. I think he was what's called a
an intelligence peddler or an
intelligence broker, but a more
sophisticated one. What an intelligence
peddler is normally is, let's say you
are a Pakistani guy and you work in a
restaurant and two al-Qaeda guys come
into the restaurant. They have lunch and
you hear something. You go to the
American embassy and you say, "Listen,
I've got this bit of information. I want
to I want to talk to a C CIA officer."
So John comes downstairs uh and I say,
"What do you have?" and um you give me
the information. Okay, sounds plausible.
I'm going to give you a few hundred for
your trouble. But then you go to the
British embassy and do the same thing.
And then the French embassy and then the
Russian embassy and then the Chinese
embassy and you've just made six months
worth of salary, right? That's an
intelligence peddler.
Epstein would have been far far more
sophisticated than that. and his
intelligence is not coming from two
al-Qaeda guys having lunch. It's coming
from Bill Clinton and Bill Gates and
Alan Dersowitz and Prince Andrew and all
of these other movers and shakers that
he was constantly in touch with.
Now, who who would it have been for?
Well, we now know from these documents
that [snorts] through his attorney, he
was actively seeking an admission by the
CIA that he was somehow associated with
the CIA. and and they did the same thing
with the National Security Council. It
doesn't look like they ever got a
response.
>> They foyed them when he went to jail
>> in summer 2019. And he foy this is what
was interesting. He foyed them
for the dates between sometime in 2000
and 2014.
Now, here's why this was interesting to
me, John, because there there's a bigger
point I don't want to get lost, but a
little tangent.
I've I'm very open-minded on this now
because I I agree with you. I think
we're seeing a lot more. And I think
like I saw Dave Smith tweet out
something that would have seemed crazy a
few weeks ago and now I'm like that's
not crazy. Where he said, "I used to
think Epstein worked for MSAD. Now I
wonder if MSAD worked for Epstein." I
don't think I'm there. However, it does
feel like there wasn't a I used the word
employee in my question. It does not
feel like there was an employee
relationship. That's
>> I agree. And and that's one of the
things that I've I've changed in my own
mind, not an employee of Mossad. We know
from these latest documents that he had
some sort of association with MI5 and
MI6, essentially the FBI and the CIA of
the UK.
>> That's right.
>> We know that he made an approach to the
German intelligence service. And we know
that he tried hard to get a one-on-one
meeting with Vladimir Putin. They went
back and forth and back and forth and
finally the Russians agreed that he
could meet with Putin and three other
people and he said no, it has to be just
Putin and the Russians said no.
What the [__] is that all about? Why
would he what what would he have to say
to Vladimir Putin that is so sensitive
that the head of the, you know, SVR
couldn't be in the room? He had to say
it directly to Putin.
>> All right, let me throw a fishing line
out here. That's all this is, people.
It's a fishing line. You don't have to
bite on this. So, I had David Sadder in
for episodes 92
and 133 back in 2022. I don't know how
you remember the episode numbers. I
don't remember who I interviewed a week
ago and I see the the icon pop up on my
thing and I'm like, I have no idea who
[laughter] that is.
>> I have a photographic audiovisisual
memory. It helps. But David Sadder
was actually roommates with Bill Clinton
or on the same hall as Bill Clinton at
Oxford and knew him and then later had
some issues with Clinton which was
interesting. Really a nice guy. I like
David.
>> David became the chief Moscow
correspondent for the Financial Times in
1976.
>> Wow.
>> He was then kicked out of the Soviet
Union in somewhere the area 8788. He was
one of the last people uncicked out
after it flipped over to being Russia
again, but came back and as Russia was
rebuilding itself, if you want to call
it that, became the preeminent
psychologist of Putin in the Western
world. He eventually became the first
Western journalist to be banned from
Russia in December 2013. conveniently
right before Maidon when he was at the
Ukrainian embassy looking to go back
into Russia. Basically, he got the FSB
line where they're like, I forget what
the exact line was. It was like 15
minutes into episode 92. It was very
dramatic, but like it was something like
whoa, okay, you're going to get whacked
if you go in there.
>> And so David obviously has a lot of
strong opinions because
Putin literally killed some of his
friends. Boris Nemov was someone he was
tight with. Anipalit Skaya was someone
he was tight with,
>> right? So obviously he doesn't like him
at all and I fully understand that. But
I was after David was there the first
time I was reading one of his books and
I forget which one it was but there was
a little mention in there that just made
my like the hairs on on my arm go up.
Six months before that maybe I had been
reading this series by Henry Abbott
about the relationship between Jeffrey
Epstein and Apollo Global. That ring a
bell?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So Drexel Burnham Lambert becomes
the guys who found Leon Black all that.
>> Basically Henry Abbott was a
>> is a a basketball reporter. He had a
blog on ESPN called True Hoop. I used to
read this when I was a kid and then ESPN
laid off everybody in the 2010s because
they lost money. So he just kept his
blog and did it from the outside. So he
sees that some guys from Apollo Global
get on the ownership of like three
different NBA teams. And in 2020 he's
like, "That's interesting. They're kind
of connected to Epstein. Let me do an
investigation in that."
>> Oh my god.
>> He's planning on doing a two or
three-part investigation. [__] guy
goes nuts. It becomes a 21 chapter
investigation. Some of the greatest [__]
I have ever read in my life. And one of
the things that he really outlined and
it was sourced out the [__] wazoo was
the whole Adnan Kosogible thing and the
Admin I've been waiting to bring this up
the whole time. The Admin relationship
with Jeffrey Epstein from an arms
dealing p perspective from a sex
trafficking perspective from an
international like government
communication perspective. So fast
forward again back six months later I'm
reading David's book and he mentions
this one war that was like war. It was
like one day Yeah. that happened in the
middle of like the second Chetchin war
when Putin's basically seizing power at
the time as a wartime leader and then
eventually is able to move up the
elections and get into the off get into
office but some I forget even what it
was but some army invaded that was
related to Russia correct me if I'm
wrong in the comments but it was
something like this basically like
invaded Dagistan
>> with a bunch of helicopters dropped you
know a few bombs or something and then
left and they were going to come back.
But a meeting was organized between the
Russian government and the Dagasanis
in either Monte Carlo or Nice.
>> Seriously,
>> at the home of Adnan Kosigible. And he
just had it in there.
>> That is a very that is a stereotypical
Adnan Kosogible thing to do.
>> And why would that be for people out
there who are not familiar with Adnan
Kosogi?
>> Adnan Kashogi. His actual name in Arabic
is is Kashuki.
Um Saudi um Saudi arms dealer, Saudi
man about the world, uh fixer, friend of
kings and presidents and prime
ministers, the uncle of Jamal Kashoki,
who was the Washington Post uh columnist
whacked by the Saudi crown prince. I
>> believe he's a cousin to Dodie Fed, too.
>> No.
>> Did I just say that out loud?
>> Can we Google that?
>> Is that true? Did I make that up? I
might have made that up. Kosogible
related to Dodie Fiad. [laughter]
>> So,
you know, when
>> he's the maternal uncle.
>> No way. The Fiads are Egyptians.
>> Yeah. Uncle and nephew.
I'll just pull it up for you.
right here.
>> Saudi arms dealer Adnan Kosigible was
the maternal uncle of Dodie Fied, making
them uncle and nephew rather than
cousins. Dodie Fied's mother was Samira
Kashogi,
>> who was the sister of Adashi, the actual
uncle and nephew.
>> And Dodie Fied was the man that Princess
Diana was dating who was killed
alongside her in Claris.
>> I never knew that. I never knew that.
>> Continue, John.
>> So,
>> it's all tied together. [screaming]
It is.
>> IT'S ALL TIED.
>> THE world's not a not a big place.
>> No.
>> So when when Congress passed a law in
1983 that we could no longer arm the
Contra rebels, Colonel Oliver North, who
was the Pentagon designate to the
National Security Council, decided to um
just go around the law. And he did that
by contacting Adnan Koshokchi and
organizing a very complicated operation
whereby
we would sell arms to the Iranians which
was against the law. Uh we would do that
through Kashokchi.
He used his own bank account in Cyprus
to take payment for the for the weapons
and then he would give the money. He
would take you know 10% for himself. he
was Mr. 10%. He would take the money and
then transfer it to accounts controlled
by Oliver North and um John Po Dexter
and uh Admiral Richard Cord all from the
National Security Council and then use
that money to buy arms on the gray
market to send to the Contrabels. It was
all illegal. Everybody was indicted.
Nobody really was punished even though
they were indicted. and uh an Kashokchi
just took his money and smiled and got
back on the yacht and steamed around the
Mediterranean.
>> He's a he's a fixer among many other
things, but who
>> he worked for himself?
>> Mhm.
>> Who did he most
assist in his efforts? I genuinely don't
know the answer.
>> Probably us.
>> Okay.
>> I mean, he was very very close to the
Saudi royal family. Of course, he was a
Saudi is a Saudi. I think he's still
alive. Um although he's got to be really
old by now. Um
he was very close to the Saudi uh
leadership.
He's deceased now. Oh yeah. 2017. Yeah.
He was pretty old.
Yeah. He wasn't that old. 83
82. So um
he was one of these guys like Mark Rich
who would just deal with anybody who had
money, anybody who could pay. So he
would work with the Israelis, he would
work with the Americans, he would work
with, you know, anybody, [snorts] the
Libyans, the North Koreans. It just it
didn't make any difference.
>> Now
there there's two guys though cuz what
you're talking about also with Iran
Contra ties into that Al Yama deal
>> that happened which was around the same
area. I'll come back to that. But
there's there's two guys
that Epstein comes into contact with
upon leaving Bear Sterns who basically
seemed to cut his teeth in arms dealing
and I'll say sex trafficking. He
probably already had pretty good
expertise in moneyaundering which he
seemed to learn well when he was on Wall
Street. But it's Kosogible and English
pronunciation there and
Douglas Lease. Yeah, I don't know him
>> in Britain. So, Douglas Lee, I [__] I
should have had this. There's a guy who
did an amazing 20 minute like
documentary on YouTube outlining this
whole thing. I want to find it so that
we can give him credit. But I had
[snorts] heard about this before.
Douglas Lee was a guy that Epste claimed
to have a falling out with later who was
basically like a British fixer and arms
dealer who took in Jeffrey. I forget how
he got introduced to him, but it was at
the same time as Hashogi and they
started then the Iran Contra thing came
in and the Alyama deal came in in Saudi
Arabia and what happened later is that
Epstein's fake passport which is like
Maurice or something whatever was
recovered which they which you can
deduce from the time it would have had
to be provided to be that good by some
sort of intelligence service. Is that
fair to say? Absolutely. in the early
80s
>> and they were able to afterwards chart
with the information we've gotten
through files chart all of Epstein's
movements through countries directly
related to Saudi getting to Saudi Arabia
on all the right dates to help in some
way for this deal to go through
is he not working for anyone because
there's something I'm going to bring up
after this but at that point is he just
a guy who's getting introduced to these
other independent contractors and
therefore just working for them and it
serves whatever purpose it serves or do
you think at that point perhaps he was
already working with MSAD or CIA or
both? Oh, I think the latter,
especially Mossad, they're very good at
spotting talent. They really are. A lot
of thought goes into this kind of thing.
And you know, the way the way his career
moved as quickly as it did, the way he
accumulated wealth at a fantastic speed,
>> right,
>> tells me that he connected with an
official body early on
>> when I was at the CIA, I never ever
heard of Jeffrey Epstein. Never. Not
once. Now, that doesn't necessarily mean
anything. Um, but never once did his
name ever come up. And you know, for for
a while I was up on the seventh floor
spending all day every day with the
director, the deputy director, the
deputy director for operations, the
chief of staff, the, you know, executive
director, the deputy executive director.
These are serious people. They're
running the CIA. And it never ever ca
came up even off-handedly.
>> Kashi we talked about a lot.
>> I to so [sighs] so you did talk about
Hashoi a lot.
>> What was the context to that? Usually
>> he could do anything. He could do
anything and he was willing to do
anything so long as there was a nice fat
paycheck for him at the end.
>> Right. Mhm.
>> I had asked another guy I know
who had who was at FBI if he had come
across he was like, "Oh yeah, there's a
flowchart on that big time."
>> Aliyama was
so huge. I mean, everybody knew about
Alyama. And Aliyama was also very
public.
The the
>> What was the nature of that deal? Again,
it was likeund [snorts]
>> uh maybe I'm I don't want to get the
number wrong that deal. Can Can we Can
we just so I can refresh my own memory
too?
600,000 barrels. So 600,000 barrels of
crude oil per day to the British
government.
uh name of a series of record arm sales
by the United Kingdom to Saudi Arabia,
paid for by the delivery of up to
600,000 barrels of crude oil per day to
the British government. The prime
contractor has been Bay Systems and its
predecessor British Aerospace. The first
sales occurred in September 1985 and the
most recent contract for 72 Euro Fighter
Typhoon multi-roll fighters was signed
in August 2006.
>> So this goes on for a long
>> decades.
>> Decades. Yeah.
>> And part of what Prince Andrew is now
being accused of when he was trade envoy
for 10 years is covering up or refusing
to share information as it pertains to
Jeffrey Epstein's involvement in the
Aliyama deal.
>> That's right. So, what see this is yet
another question that we're probably not
going to get an answer to. What could
Jeffrey Epstein possibly have been able
to contribute
in the in the Alyama deal? I've been
thinking about almost nothing else for
the last seven hours.
>> The right nationalities,
>> right?
>> You know,
>> he did kind of have that thing though
where especially back then when he had
the fro going and all that where you
could kind of blend. I'll give him that.
>> Right. But he had a [snorts] he had
he had those manipulation skills with
people where and also John I don't know
maybe you could speak to this better cuz
you can look at this from an espionage
perspective because you're trained to
think like that but in regular in the
regular world right which espionage
occurs in the regular world
>> guys like him when you hear him talk the
Coney Island accent the all shucks kind
of whatever just on the surface when you
don't disarming Right.
>> Absolutely. That's all part of the part
of the thing, part of the delivery, part
of the training. Sure. There's something
about that. It reminded me in a
different way of of my friend Luis
Navia, who was here in episodes 221 and
222. He was like the chief smuggler for
the cartels, except the Asian ones, his
quote, not mine, around [snorts] the
world until 2000 when he was taken down
in Operation Journey in Venezuela by
like [__] 15 countries. But he
>> [snorts]
>> He walks up, you think he's a mix
between Francis Ford Copela and Mr.
Magcoo. He never carried a gun. He
wasn't the violent guy. And he'd just be
like, "Oh, what the fuck?" And people
were like, "I can't even No, like Luis,
we're holding He would tell these
stories." And they're like, "No, Luis,
we're going to kill you." And he's like,
"Listen, bro. I I got places to be like,
can we go to the bar or something?" And
they'd be like this [__] guy. And
they just wouldn't.
>> Some are unflapable,
>> right?
>> Yeah. And it's I think there's a little
something like that in Jeffrey Epstein
where people even from a totally
different background, worldview or you
know political desires, they'd get in a
room with him and they're like the
[__] balls on this guy.
>> Could you see that?
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah. Although,
yeah, I could see that through the first
arrest even. But then
he [snorts] had to have concluded that
things were so bad in 2019 that this
this was it. It was over.
You know
>> why? Why do you say that?
>> Cuz he killed himself.
>> You do believe he did?
>> I do. I believe he killed himself.
>> What makes you believe that considering
all the evidence that they have? See,
but the evidence
the evidence isn't as clear as I think
most people would want it to be. For
example, and I base this on my own
experience in the federal prison system.
>> Mhm.
>> The guards, number one, have their heads
up their asses 24 hours a day. The only
qualification to be a prison guard in
the federal system, the Federal Bureau
of Prisons, is you have to be working on
a GED
and no uh felony convictions. That's it.
There's this rule
that prisoners can't touch the mail,
right? So, we have mail call every day
at 4:00 and the guards are supposed to
say your name and hand you your mail.
Most of the time the guards didn't do
mail call. Prisoners did mail call in
violation of the rule of the rules. Any
idea why? Because they couldn't read.
It was as simple as that. The guards
couldn't competence basically.
>> Yeah. I mean, they literally could not
read to call out the names. So, number
one, they're idiots. Number two, the
cameras are always broken. Always. I was
a janitor in the uh chapel when I was in
prison. And every day part of my job was
to go in there and break up guys having
sex in the chapel.
>> In the chapel.
>> Yeah. Because
>> Jesus
>> of the Lord.
>> That's what I said. You guys, this is
God's house for heaven's sake.
[laughter]
>> What are you going to do? But the reason
they would all be having sex in the
chapel is because they knew that the
cameras didn't work. [laughter] None of
the cameras work.
The guards are supposed to be doing
their rounds every 15 minutes or if
there's a suicide watch situation going
on every 8 minutes. And with Epstein,
they it was like two hours before they
finally made their rounds. Why? because
number one, they're either jacking off
in the uh in the guard booth, which
happens all the freaking time, or
they're sound asleep in the guard booth,
or they're on the phone with their
girlfriends, or they're surfing the
internet.
So, no, they don't they don't make the
rounds. And then people are like, "Oh,
but there's a glitch. You know, there's
this one second glitch." Yeah, because
every night the cameras reset
themselves. They're old cameras. They
still use tape and they tape over
yesterday's.
>> Then why don't they let the guards talk?
Why were the guards like
>> Oh, they would never let the Because the
guards are I just stopped myself from
saying a word that's not supposed to be
>> [__]
>> These guys are so stupid.
You know, a a guard from the prison
where I was um emailed me. He he saw one
of the one of the podcasts and he said,
"This is exactly why we wanted to kill
you."
And I said, "Bring it, tough guy."
>> Why he wanted to kill you?
>> Yeah. Cuz I say they're morons and
retards and this and that. And it's all
true. [laughter]
It's true. Learn to read and then maybe
we can have a conversation. [laughter]
I mean, otherwise, put up. Let's go. I'm
not afraid of these guys.
But this is why everything [snorts] went
wrong. Because what we saw go wrong the
night Jeffrey Epstein died
goes wrong every night. It's the same
thing.
>> But so perfectly like that. You think it
could line up that way?
>> Yes. I saw it. I saw it. For example,
not supposed to have microwaves in the
housing unit, right?
>> Mhm.
>> And then people are like, "Ah, you know,
you [__] long enough, they're going to
they're going to put in a microwave." So
they put in a microwave. All right.
There was a serial killer in my unit and
he took a liking to me inexplicably.
[laughter]
So we called him truck because he was a
long-distance truck driver and he would
murder prostitutes all along his route
and he got caught. So
So he would be like, "Hey John, uh he
had these like rotten black little nubs
for teeth. John, uh, I saved you a seat
in the TV room. Watch the Steelers game.
I'm like, thanks, Truck. Or, uh, hey,
there's a new classic rock station. I
know you like classic rock. It's 1600
a.m. Thank you, Truck.
Truck hated hated hated pedophiles.
Hated them. Fully a third of the prison
is pedophiles because remember, they're
all at the low security level,
>> right?
So,
there's like this rule in prison. No
pedophiles are allowed in the TV room.
And pedophiles aren't even allowed in
their own room unless it's to sleep.
Okay? So, if you're a pedophile and it's
the middle of the day, get the [__] out
of the room.
>> Well, there's a pedophile in his room
[snorts]
and the guy's like blah blah blah blah
blah. He won't stop talking. Well,
another thing is pedophiles aren't
allowed to have any visitors in their
rooms. You can't have another pedophile
cuz they're going to talk about
pedophilia, which is what they do. They
relive their crimes every single day.
>> They [clears throat] like they can't
help themselves.
So,
this pedophile is just yapping away and
Truck is getting angrier and angrier and
angrier.
And finally, the pedophile lays down for
a nap. Truck had gone to the commissary
and he bought a bottle of olive oil,
which is $2.85.
You can because everybody cooks in their
cells.
>> Plastic or glass?
>> Plastic.
>> So he pours the olive oil into a bowl
and he microwaves it. So it's boiling.
Like literally it's bubbling, boiling,
scalding oil and he pours it on the
pedophile's face while he's sleeping.
And the guy, the scream, I'll never
forget the scream. And his skin is just
like dropping off of his skull.
and pedophile got a pedophile. The
pedophile got, you know, medevaced to
Pittsburgh. They landed a helicopter in
the yard and medevaced him to
Pittsburgh. Truck got another 10 years
onto the 40 he was already doing for
being a serial killer.
>> He was only doing 40 as a serial killer.
>> I know, right?
>> He had a great lawyer.
>> Yeah, he did. But the point is that
there are rules for everything and
[snorts] nobody pays any attention to
them and nothing works the way it's
supposed to.
>> Then why does the Justice Department
come out and say things like, "Oh,
here's all the evidence." And then they
show that they didn't put all the
evidence. And I'm just talking about
like that.
>> But then that proves my point because
people are idiots at every single level.
>> It doesn't matter if you went to Harvard
Law School, you can still be an idiot,
>> right? And another thing too, this is
this is a lesson that that government
officials, especially senior government
officials, just cannot learn. And it is
that the cover up of the crime is always
worse than the crime.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Always.
You know,
>> a lie get begets 10 more lies begets a
hundred more lies.
>> And Richard Nixon didn't resign because
of Watergate. Richard Nixon resigned
because of the cover up of Watergate. H
I think it's the same situation here.
All right. Well, let me flip it around
on you.
I have always thought
still do think that Jeffrey Epstein is
dead. I
>> and I feel pretty comfortable.
>> I spoke to his brother recently and I
said I said, "Is he dead?"
>> And he's like, "He's dead. I I
identified the body." I'm just
>> I mean, I spoke to OJ. I didn't speak to
him, but he said he didn't do it. You
know what I mean? Like identified the
body. He said, "I think he was
murdered."
And that's a debate, you know, that he
wanted to have with me. But he said,
"Yeah, he's dead. I identified his body.
I took it to the crematorium."
>> Joseph Scott Morgan, friend of mine,
broke this down. He's a medical death
investigator. He broke it down like
scientifically with all the bones, the
hyoid bone and all that about what would
not make sense about it being suicide
and therefore it being murder.
Obviously, Dr. Michael Boden who's like
the goat with all this.
>> He's the goat.
>> Also does not think
>> that he killed himself. So it's
possible.
>> It's at least possible that he was
killed.
>> It's possible. Definitely.
>> Absolutely.
>> Now, I do think he's dead.
>> Mhm.
>> But again, this whole thing is just like
you you almost have to open your mind to
[__] everything. That's crazy. So,
I'll ask it like this.
If you were tasked, not that you ever
would be, it's hypothetical people, but
if you were tasked with making the world
believe that Jeffrey Epstein was dead
and getting him out of that prison
without anyone knowing to wherever he's
going to go to get [__] facial
surgery and live out his life, how would
you do it? Oh, you would take out the
body, whether it's a a body double or,
you know, made out of silicone or
whatever. take it out in full view of
everybody. [snorts]
That's how I would do it. Let as many
people as possible see this body
so that reasonable people can agree to
disagree.
>> They did do that.
>> Mhm. And there was a New York Post
reporter very ready to go.
>> And there was the conversation about the
ear, which I've heard a thousand million
times.
>> Those ones I'm always a little skeptical
of because they can doctor them,
>> of course. Well, it's like this stupid
obviously AI generated picture of him
just like walking down the street in Tel
Aviv.
>> Oh, yeah. That one that one's not real.
But I'm saying like So the recipe you
just gave me though
>> Mhm.
>> is in line. It's not to say that's what
happened.
>> That's what they did.
>> Yeah. Sure.
>> Yeah. Cuz I had another guy in here, Ken
Gibson, who's worked in media forever,
and he's like, the idea that a New York
Post reporter on an early Saturday
morning in [__] August was that ready
to go immediately after this? Yeah,
sketchy. And another thing too is if I
wanted
if I wanted to initiate a cover up of
this scale,
I would
cremate whatever it is I took out on
that gurnie because otherwise you'd be
you'd be having people say, "Okay, let's
just settle this. We're going to dig him
up. We're going to get a court order.
We're going to exume the body. We're
going to do DNA testing and make sure
that this is Jeffrey Epstein." Can't do
that. cremated.
>> I don't know anymore, John. I really
don't.
>> I have to tell you, I was [snorts] jaded
anyway because of my own personal
experience,
>> but now it's like
I don't believe anything anymore. Not at
face value anyway. Have you had your
like any kind of moment where you think
back to a bunch of stuff, different
moments and visions of like things you
did that you were certain were because
of one thing in one way and one person
in one mission that you're now like,
"Wait a minute. Why was that guy there,
too?"
>> I think about that kind of thing all the
time.
>> Yeah, I do. And in some cases, it's
taken years for me to finally conclude
like, "Oh crap, that's what that was
about."
>> I've thought about this Rockefeller
thing a million times.
>> Yeah.
>> You know,
I I've told you the story. It It was the
one and only time I ever received a
phone call from Coen Powell. I told you
the story.
>> I You told the internet in The New Voice
as well.
>> Yeah. And in The New Voice. But I think
about that a lot, too.
>> Yeah. you know, and and I remember when
it first happened, I remember thinking,
"This wasn't your fault. Don't let it
bother you." And it's bothered me for
decades.
>> It's human lives. You're a real person.
>> Yeah.
>> The story was that Coen Powell asked how
to target someone in Iraq. John said
what it was and
>> gave him his address
>> and then he found out eight of them got
bombed later. [laughter]
>> There was one time dozens of cruise
missiles, you know, vaporized the
building. Every time I watch that clip,
I think of the [__] uh Mark Wahlberg
line that departed. Yeah, it can send a
[__] cruise middle missile up the ass
of a camel from a thousand yards away.
[laughter] Thousand miles away.
>> Not to get too far off the topic, but
the assassination of Zoahi, the number
two in al-Qaeda.
>> Oh yeah.
>> You know, we shot him with a with a
drone launched missile, right?
>> The missile had no warhead on it,
>> right? We did that on purpose because we
didn't want to kill the women and
children inside the apartment. He came
out onto the balcony to smoke a
cigarette. Fired the missile at him. It
went completely through his body. A
missile went completely through his
body. And with no warhead, there was no
explosion. Can you imagine cleaning up
that mess? [laughter]
I appreciate the uh [laughter]
responsibility on that one.
At least they didn't hit a wedding.
>> Oh, we did.
>> Was a little better than the Obama year.
>> They hit every every wedding during
Obama.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it was uh that was
interesting. But the thing I had wanted
to bring it to when I was bringing up
the early origins of Jeffrey Epstein
with that Alama deal is obviously
>> the point there is that there is some
sort of relationship with intelligence
intelligences.
>> Absolutely. at the time and there is a
tweet sent it to you. Yep. He has it up.
So, this is from Ronald Reagan
>> about Iran Contra. Okay.
>> In his new auto and this is from back in
the day obviously because he's dead. Uh
in the new autobiography, former
President Ronald Reagan says Israel was
the instigator and prime mover in the
Iran Contra affair. He blames the
Israelis for misleading him into
believing he was selling arms to
so-called Iranian moderates when some
quote may have had links to the
Ayatollah Kameese government and were
trying to obtain weapons under false
pretenses unquote. Israel began the arms
deals with Iran when it contacted Robert
McFarland Reagan's national security
adviser to propose the first sale and
continued to press the secret dealings
thereafter. Reagan writes in an American
life that Prime Minister Shimon Perez
was behind the proposal. The former
president says Iranian middlemen
endorsed by Israel helped quote win the
freedom of three hostages unquote.
Reagan adds, but the same middlemen
behaved at times like bait and switch
conmen with the sole intentions of
profiterian. So with Ryan Contra, they
were trying to get weapons to the sand
and east as in South America. And they
were trying to do it by financing $150
million deal to with through Iran when
we weren't supposed to be dealing with
postrevolution Iran in the 80s. That's
like the very highlevel version of it.
But
>> it says down here too, Patrick Ali says
that that Epstein was was roommates with
uh with Stanley Potinger.
He was in up to his neck in Iran Contra.
Roommates partners and roommates with J.
Stanley Pottinger who helped ship
weapons to Iran prior to Iran Contra.
Can we read this, Steve?
>> Good grief.
>> So, according to his former friend, the
journalist Jesse Cornbluth, who's
Epsteined up the ass.
>> Yep.
>> In pause. In the mid 1980s, Epstein said
he worked
>> he worked for governments to recover
money looted by African dictators and
occasionally subcontracted to those same
autocrats to help them hide their stolen
money. A source who spoke with
journalist Vicky Ward from Vanity Fair
the 03 piece said one of Epstein's
clients was the late Saudi arms dealer
Hashogi a middleman in the in the Iran
Contra scandal who helped smuggle cash
for the Marcos family out of the
Philippines in 1988. Hashigi was
arrested in Switzerland. That's hard to
do for concealing assets and later faced
fraud and racketeering charges in the
US. He was later acquitted. Must had a
great attorney. That year he sold his
200 He sold his 282 foot yacht to the
Sultan of Brun who soon flipped it to
Donald Trump. And let's go to the next
one right here. Epstein was fired from
Bear Sterns around the time he met
Douglas Lee who I was telling you about.
Epstein then started a short-lived
partnership with Jay Stanley Pottinger,
a former US Department of Justice
official who was investigated for his
role in dealing arms to the Islamic Pro
Republic of Iran. The Iran Contra affair
appears to be a pivotal moment in in
Epstein's life. Between 81 and '86, the
Reagan administration covertly sold arms
to Iran, which was at war with Saddam
Hussein's Iraq. So, they were selling to
the Iranians they didn't like cuz they
liked Saddam Hussein even less.
>> My question is, why is he this didn't
wasn't clocking to me at first because I
looked at this very quickly before we
got on air. Why is Reagan saying that
that benefited the Israelis when the
Israelis really don't like the Iranian
regime? Like that has always been their
big bug. the but the Iranians back then
didn't have a nuclear program and it was
Iraq that was the real like immediate
threat to to Israel because the Iraqis
did have a nuclear program and a
biological weapons program and a
chemical weapons program and they were
working with a Belgian inventor named
Gerald Bull to um to
the the Iraqis were to build something
called the the big gun.
>> This is one of the very first things I
learned about my first week uh at the
CIA. Gerald Bull created this this giant
gun that was so big you just had to sort
of lean the barrel up against the side
of a mountain, point it in essentially
the right direction, and then fire it.
And it it would send a shell as far as a
missile would go. And nobody wanted to
buy it. They're like, "What are we going
to do with this giant gun?" Right? It's
as big as a house. And so the Iraqis
said, "We'll take it."
And so the Iraqis bought this thing and
before
it kept cracking when when Bull would
would test it, it kept cracking. So, he
came up with this idea to put what he
called a condom on the inside of the gun
to smooth the barrel and to and to keep
the the reverberation from the shot from
cracking it. But before he could test it
with the condom inside, the Israelis
assassinated him.
>> They're pretty good at that.
>> Yeah. Gerald Bull and his giant gun.
I remember saying to my boss, like I
say, I was only on the job for a week. I
said, "This is a joke, right?" And he
said, "No, no, this is deadly serious.
It's a giant gun. They have to lean it
up on the side of the mountain to fire
it."
>> I'm picturing that thing in Game of
Thrones they were trying to take the
dragon out with [laughter] just like,
"Come on, baby. Let's go."
>> All right. So,
[laughter]
you had always maintained
that Jeffrey Epstein was a MSAD access
agent.
>> Do you think I wanted to bring this up
first so we at least had the context of
what Ronald Reagan said about this?
>> Probably his handler said about it
because I don't think he was all there
by the time he wrote that book.
>> Yeah. Not a chance. So, so do you think
that in something like that, if in fact
the Israelis had an interest in seeing
Iraq be
neutralized more, do you think that this
is the prime type of situation where he
could have been recruited at that time?
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah.
>> Do you think that's what happened? You
know, when you're when you put all of
these episodes together in a line, that
would make sense to me.
>> Yes.
>> Next question.
This is a deal where the CIA is running
a lot of ops as well, meaning they have
to know he's involved with this.
>> You know, that's a good question.
He would have had to have bumped up
against CIA ops people or even if not
CIA ops people, NSC people who were in
up to their necks in this thing.
>> National Security Council.
>> National Security Council, you know, the
likes of of um as I said, Admiral Po
Dexter, Richard Cord, uh Oliver North,
all these guys. So even if if you're not
dealing directly with agency people,
although you probably would be, you're
going to at least be dealing with White
House people.
Now, you had said earlier
you had never heard Jeffrey Epstein
mentioned at CIA. You did hear Hashigi
mentioned though a bunch
>> all the time.
>> Hashigi was also like extremely public
for throughout a lot of his life.
>> That's right.
If
seven people from the NSC and CIA
directly dealt or at least bumped into
Jeffrey Epstein during said mission,
Iran Contra, which was a cover up. They
were covering up something they were
doing.
>> That's right. The comp is it reasonable
to say that the compartmentalization
structure of espionage bureaucracy in
the United States government would mean
that those people would chart this maybe
have it in their own files but not
necessarily share it with anybody.
>> Yes. And I could tell you exactly how
that would play out. If I were one of
the agency guys involved and I run into
this
American guy who's in the middle of it
and he's not with us and he's not with
the White House people, then who the
hell is he with? So, what I would have
done is I first would have gone to the
White House people and say, "Who's this
American, this Epstein guy?" And then I
would have gone to the FBI and say,
"Listen, just so you know, we're doing
this highly compartmentalized
top secret operation. You don't need to
know what it's about, but you do need to
know that there is a private citizen
involved who's an American
just so you can start a file on him,
just in case this is going to be a
counter intelligence problem for us in
the future." [clears throat]
It doesn't look like that was ever done.
I can't imagine why.
>> That was going to be my next question.
What would be something
>> he had to have had protection at the
White House? He had to have
>> at that time
>> way back then, sometime between 1981 and
198, you know, four or five.
>> All right. Wait a second. That would
make sense for a second. So if he has
protection at the White House, maybe
through a technical intermediary like
Oliver North or something like that.
Exactly.
>> They're doing this under the table. It's
a crime. So, he's going to be like, it's
more like the mob. Like, all right, I'm
not saying nothing.
>> I know who that guy is, but I can't tell
people I know who that guy is. Cuz then
they'll say, "How do you know who that
guy is?" And now we got a problem.
>> That's right.
>> Okay. That's right. See, you know, I had
never thought of that.
>> That's interesting.
>> But now that we're playing it out,
>> Yeah.
>> that makes sense to me.
>> This is why you're here.
>> So, I had always, again, my mind is very
open on all this. I am not married to
any of this stuff. what I had always
thought just very 30,000 foot view in
the air and some people have misheard me
on recent episodes on how I explain this
so I need to do a better job. I'd always
looked at it like okay he's working with
MSAD or and you have to say this or with
other intelligence organizations in
Israel because they're not the only one.
That's right.
>> Like Jonathan Pard wasn't with MSAD was
with the military.
>> That's right. It was military. Same [__]
but different name. That's right. But
MSD's an important, you know, we have
what 18 different intelligence agencies,
>> right? You you would think one or two
might be enough, but that's
>> But I always thought he worked with
them. And then the thing that really
shifted things for Jeffrey Epstein and
his timeline was the I believe September
2002 flight with Bill Clinton, Kevin
Spacy, and Chris Tucker, which made page
six. Prior to then, Jeffrey Epstein was
known as a New York City socialite and
not known publicly. He was known on the
socialite circles, which
>> by the way, when someone's known as a
socialite in New York, red flag should
be flying. But
>> he's he's a in this case a good spy.
He's doing all his sick [__] He's going
to the White House 18 times. No one
knows who the [__] the guy is and
everything. And then all of a sudden,
boom, flight happens. page six story.
Then he has to do the interview with
Vicky Ward in March 2003. He's out
there. No coincidence in some ways that
his case starts coming up in '05 in
Florida cuz he's a known guy in some
respects. And so my thought always was,
and if I were a betting man, I would
have said it was probably late 90s when
Clinton was still in office. My bet
always was that CIA was asleep at the
wheel. Maybe because of the
compartmentalization we just talked
about. And you know, then they probably
find out, maybe it's 1996. I'll put a
year on it. 97. They find out so far
this guy's been to the Clinton White
House 15 times, maybe.
>> They're like, "Who the fuck?"
>> Yeah. Who's this?
>> It's this guy and the British lady who's
whose dad ran the Daily Mirror and he
started all the [__] peer reviews and
runs all our kids textbooks in America
and got buried on [laughter] the Mount
of Olives in [__] Israel 5 days after
he got pushed off a boat.
>> Why is this [__] coming in with
the guy who's taking [__] from the
[__] intern? You know, imagine the
stories that you could piece together if
you had unfettered access just to the
visitor log.
>> Just to that.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Right. So, someone
Linda at Langley, right,
>> goes, "Wait a minute. We got a problem."
Takes it up the chain of command
suddenly says, "Boss, I don't know who
the [__] this guy is." They then take 10
minutes to look into it and they're
like, "Oh my god, he's running a [__]
pedal ring at the behest of the Victoria
Secret guy in [__] New York City."
And holy [__] he's involved with Iran
Contra. He's [__] working with MSAD.
He seems to be an intelligence dealer.
The [__] wife, who's not really the
wife's a problem. She's connected up the
ass to all this [__]
>> Oh my god. THEY GOT DIRT ON EVERYONE,
including the current president. This is
a crisis the likes of which if we outed
this everything could fall. Sounds very
familiar today by the way.
>> Yes it does.
>> So they say in that moment now I you
know I proposed the New Jersey solution.
I'm like just [__] blow his brains
out,
>> right? [clears throat]
>> You know say to Msad, what are you going
to do about it?
>> I know a lot of guys that would do that,
>> right? Okay, good. I don't know where
they were at this time. You know, we
could have called up [__] Vinnie and
Roco. They didn't take care of
>> mentioned exactly what I was thinking.
>> That's right. But they didn't do that.
And this is what I just always posited.
And it's a theory. I I can't say like,
"Yo, I got evidence this happened." But
I'm like, they looked at it and they
said, "Oh shit." And they go to the guy
and they go, "All right, you know that
we know that you know that we know that
you know that we know what you're doing
here. And you know that we know that you
know that we know that you [__] have
been doing this a long time and you
could take down the whole system if we
tell people about that." And so you know
that we know that you know that we know
that now we're in a Mexican standoff.
>> And so here's the deal. You're going to
have to keep doing whatever it is the
[__] you do, but now you pay a tax.
You're on our soil. You're going to give
us some information, too.
>> And so now, what John, what did he
foyer? He foyed the years 2000 to 2014.
>> Pretty interesting to me,
>> I'll say.
>> Am I crazy or am I crazy?
>> No, it's a it's a great catch. And it
also would tend to implicate both the
Bush and the Clinton administrations.
>> That's right.
>> Sorry. Bush and Obama.
>> Wait, now you look Oh, from the years he
foyed. Okay. I thought I thought you
were talking about the backtrack of what
they didn't catch.
>> Now the backtrack. Now you've convinced
me that this started even earlier than I
thought. Right.
>> I was thinking Clinton
>> and it's not. It's earlier.
>> It's earlier.
>> Mhm.
There were some files missing,
>> too.
>> Yep.
>> Not not just the two and a half or three
million. I mean, they're in there, but
did you see the chart of the years that
they're really missing from?
>> Mhm.
>> Can we pull up that tweet, thief?
>> Just so people can see this.
>> I have to rethink everything. I have to
rethink things that in the past I would
have said where I feel okay about this
take and now I have to look at it and
say
>> Julian that was a ice cold scalding ice
cold if you will take and this is just
one of these things like it is what it
is when I'm wrong I'm wrong this is a
data dump I'm going to simplify this for
you John because there's some more
specific details here but it is showing
basically like if you will a percentage
of data sets from the Epstein files that
are presented over the years and we can
see that there is a massive gap and
basically like you in the chart if you
will between the years of 1999
to 2001 when among other things you had
the tech bubble blow up you had I
believe that's 99 is when the Lewinsky
impeachment trials happening you have
the election of 2000 the highly
contested election of 2000 John Kiryaku
where I don't know someone Googled this
for me but I think there was a big point
of contention in Palm Beach County
>> as it pertains to that election and
that's where one Jeffrey Epstein did
happen to reside just just looking at
some things here
>> and then in 2001
you have the worst terrorist attack in
United States history in New York and DC
and in the skies over that fell over
Pennsylvania with 1993.
>> Mhm.
>> And suddenly all these files are
missing. But John, we did get an email
from 2003 that slipped through the
cracks.
>> Really?
>> Oh, you haven't seen this one?
>> No, I haven't seen it.
>> So, there's an email thief. Boom. He's
got it. He's all over it. So, this is
from 2003. Someone named Ed Epstein
sends an email to one GMAX Gilen Maxwell
saying, "Any interest in being on the
shadow commission on 911? The membership
list is secret. She responds, "Thanks
for the invite. Unfortunately, I cannot
be on the shadow commission."
A shadow commission.
It takes my breath away.
Oh my god. This should be the banner
headline.
What? What do you make of of that?
>> I don't even know what to say.
I mean, nobody believes what the 9/11
commission concluded anyway.
>> That's right. But the fact that there
was a shadow commission with a secret
membership list
and Galen Maxwell talked about it in
2003.
Why? That's what I want to know.
>> Good question. And it's like this goes
back to a compartmentalization thing
too, John, because what we do have on
the record that we know happened is
somewhere I think it was like July 6th,
2001 and maybe like August 11th, the
dates might be slightly off. There are
two meetings that occur at the White
House. One of them with Condisa Rice
where CIA sent literally tenant Kofheer
Black and some dudes who are still like
Rich Blee who's still I think
undercover.
>> That's I think that's a fake name if I
remember correctly where they tell them
an attack's coming. So like when you
look at the whole like well CIA
definitely did this. CIA had a lot of
incompetence because they didn't share
information with FBI and there's there's
a lot of issues there and they deserve a
ton of blame. But that was the one thing
in this that was always like the canary
in the coal mine for me where I'm like,
well, it couldn't have been that. Like
they they had the leadership warning
about it. So
>> yeah, they did.
>> You know, maybe it's the White House
that I I don't know.
>> But there's also advanced knowledge that
we know about from the Saudis who have
always been covered up and we know about
with the five guys from MSAD in [__]
Fort Lee who were videotaping the thing
who were sent back to Israel on November
6th, 2001.
>> That's exactly right. And I know a guy
from the office that arrested them and
to this day he wonders why the [__] they
didn't get why the [__]
>> Mhm.
>> So when I see stuff like this, I'm like,
how many countries are involved in this
thing?
>> God, this is bad.
>> And is it even countries versus is it
this trilateral elite just in general?
Like everyone wants to just immediately
say
>> it's Israel, it's Saudi Arabia, it's the
CI. How about all the above who are
working for all the above?
>> Mhm.
>> Possible.
>> Possible. Yes.
Yes.
Incredible. Sickening. I think is how
what I first said when we sat down and
started talking. This just makes me
sick.
I don't even know what to do with them.
Gmax.
>> Gmax
redacted.
>> She must have bcccded him. Jeffrey, why
would it be in the Epstein files? Why
would it be on his computer?
>> I don't know. She BCCD him.
The membership list is secret.
>> She's not even
Was she an American at the time? I don't
did she ever become an American
officially?
>> I don't know. I wonder like we talk
about this small group, you know, you
got the commerce secretary and
transition chair who just Yes. G Maxwell
is a naturalized American citizen.
>> Born in France to British and French
parents and raised in England, she moved
to the United States in ' 91 following
her father's death. She holds triple
citizenship being a citizen of the US,
UK, and France. Yeah,
>> makes sense.
>> Can say that again.
>> Yeah. So,
>> but not Israel.
>> Yeah,
[snorts]
>> man. You have a guy like Le Let who runs
the transition team as the commerce
secretary, always in Trump's ear
advising him, shares a wall with Jeffrey
Epstein for technically 21 years, but he
claims it was 14 cuz he didn't move in
till low five. who knows if even that's
true.
>> Openly lies
>> on camera just drip blood with this
dramatic story about the first and last
time I ever spent time with that man.
And then he said, "So I never dealt with
him in business, socially, or even for
philanthropy." And and what he was
really doing was remembering all the
things he did deal with him on because
now we saw it
>> on the emails of what it was. But the
guy has, as of the time of this
recording on Friday afternoon, he has
not resigned yet. still doing his job.
>> And also, we find out his sister was one
of the founding members of the Terramar
project, which was like Gen's postJ
conviction, post Jeffrey's never going
to [__] marry me project that she
did, pet project that has something to
do with the oceans that she did a
[__] TED talk on.
>> Oh my god.
>> Do these people just all like [__] each
other?
>> They must. They must.
I'm glad I don't know people like this.
>> You don't?
>> I don't. No.
No. I would feel dirty all the time.
[snorts]
>> Well, there's a guy in the middle for
Well, actually, John, we can't forget
this. Did you see what Hillary Clinton
said the other day?
>> Oh, no. What' she say?
>> She said that they have Can we play the
video, De? I did it in my solo episode.
It's coming out two days before this,
but it's worth repeating because again,
we got the picture of Gilen in the row
looking at Chelsea coming down the aisle
at her wedding. We know about the 25 to
27 flights on the Lolita Express. Yep.
We got images of Clinton all with
Epstein. Obviously, the Clintons are
their whole [__] thing. As well on
the side, that doesn't even have to do
with Epstein. We know about the 18 known
visits that happened to the White House
>> and yet he'll let's let's run it. If
Hillary Clinton says this when asked
about the links between the Clintons and
the Epstein and Epste regret the links
that there have been
>> you know we have no links we have a very
clear record that we've been willing to
talk about which my husband has said he
took some uh rides on the airplane for
his charitable work
>> for charitable work
>> I don't recall ever meeting him u
>> I did on a few occasions and thousands
of people go to the Clinton Global
Initiative. So, it to me is not is not
something that is really at the heart of
what this matter is about. They are
accused and in both cases were convicted
of horrific crimes against girls and
women. That should be the focus. And we
are more than happy to say what we know
which is very limited and totally
unrelated to their uh behavior or their
crimes. And we want to do it in public
because let's make this transparent. The
survivors deserve that. The public
deserves that. But
>> God,
[gasps]
they just lie with straight faces.
>> Straight faces.
>> Mhm.
How does a guy like Jeffrey Epstein get
so involved with with Bill Clinton
clearly before he got into office?
Yeah, it's a good question. Could he
have spotted
Bill Clinton that early on in the
process? Just another governor.
That
>> was a governor who was letting Barry
Seal fly coke planes and demean it with
no questions asked.
>> Yes. Although I always believed he was
told, "Hey, uh, we're going to do this
and you're going to say it's okay." And
he did.
>> What makes you think that?
>> Because that would have been a federal
operation. I mean, we all knew,
everybody knows now that the CIA uh was
was allowing cocaine into the country,
making its way to Los Angeles. Um, so it
would have been federal. It's not up to
a governor to say, "No, no, you can't
you can't do this." It's like, "Shut the
[__] up. We're doing [laughter] it.
>> We're going to do it and you'll become
president."
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Listen to what we say.
>> Exactly.
>> It's just always funny when Hill when
Hillary not funny, but it's kind of sick
when Hillary talks about like women and
victims and stuff like that.
>> God.
>> And then you think about the things that
both of them are actually accused of.
>> Mhm.
>> It's like,
>> come on. That's what I mean. The
political opportunism of this that I'll
call out all day. It's like nobody gets
a win here. This is
>> No, there are no good guys in this whole
thing. And then, you know, it just makes
me feel that much worse that Virginia
Duprey uh took her life. I can't even I
can't even fathom the pressure that she
was under,
you know, and she kind of cracked in
slow motion. Remember weeks in advance
of her death, she said she had been like
hit by a school bus or something. Mhm.
>> I don't remember the whole the whole
story, but she kind of cracked up right
in front of our eyes.
>> Yeah, it's it's suspicious. And
apparently also does have to be said her
husband did beat her.
>> Yeah.
>> As well.
>> Yep.
>> Yes.
>> She had confided that in in Tara Pelary,
who was a journalist that she worked
with. And so once her family released
photos of her from towards the end of
her life that included like standing
photos of her with bruises all over her,
Tara said that she did. She had promised
obviously not to say anything, but she's
like, "Now that Virginia is deceased and
her family has released these photos, I
do feel like I should also reveal that
her husband beat her all the time."
Doesn't mean she didn't
>> not something fishy there.
>> Sure.
>> You know, she she
>> Yeah, this is bad. She went after a lot
of people.
And I just, you know,
it's like these people, they see all
these things 20, 30, 40 years ahead at
their cute little [__] Bilderberg
meetings, but they couldn't see the
internet coming.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> It's kind of weird, right?
>> Yeah. Mhm.
There's a guy that's been at the middle
of all this, Steve Bannon, who I
mentioned, Henry Abbott earlier. Shout
out to Henry for turning me on to this
back in 2021, 2022.
>> And it all turned out to be true.
>> It was all true. Steve Bannon goes way
back
>> with Leon Black and all those guys. You
can trace it back to the 80s and you can
trace back the earliest investments in
things that became Cambridge Analytica
in 1992. So they were already thinking
about how to influence [snorts] people
through fear all the way back then, but
they weren't thinking about the very
tools they were building being used
against them to have the public be able
to discuss things in the open, including
the [__] they do behind closed
doors.
>> Imagine
why? That doesn't make sense to me,
though. Like, what am I missing there?
You know, one of my favorite movies is
is a 1970s sci-fi film called Soilent
Green.
>> You mentioned last time. Yep,
>> I did.
>> Mhm.
>> And um Soilent Green takes place in the
in the future. It was filmed in like
or something and I think it takes place
in 2015.
and cars, you know, float on the air and
uh the world is overpop populated and
people can't afford food. And it gives
you a pretty good depiction of
of a world that's on the brink of just
falling apart. The only thing that they
just got completely and totally wrong
was every time Charlton H, the main
character, who's a policeman, every time
he needed to make a call, he'd pull over
to the side of the road, go into a phone
booth, and make [clears throat] the
call.
>> I guess there are just some things
people don't see.
>> That's a good way to put it.
>> You know, I remember being I was in a
station in the Middle East. I was there
on temporary duty for a week, week and a
half, and there was a tech team in from
headquarters and they were installing
the first ever um email program.
>> And so everybody in the station was
gathered around this computer and
they're showing us that you you click on
this little button that had an envelope
on it and then you write in somebody's
name and hit refresh and their actual
name pops up and then you can just write
them a like a letter. It's called
electronic mail, email. And the station
chief says, "Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. Are you saying that my people
can have access to anybody they want?
They just write this electronic mail and
hit send." And the guy said, "Yes." And
the chief said, "I don't like it. I
don't like it one bit."
>> And then he sort of made this edict that
there would be none of this email
in his station. Sometimes you just don't
see it.
You just can't your brain can't
comprehend it. And maybe that's what
we're looking at here with with our 2020
hindsight.
>> I don't understand though in the 2010s
once it was a real thing like an email's
been
>> Yeah. because it's like yes, obviously
these people were talking in a way that
they didn't think the DOJ would ever
release their emails to the public.
Right? But you have people in 2021,
2022, 2023 keeping their jobs and
saying, "No, I regret my relationship,
but I didn't really know them." And now
it comes out that they did. And yet,
maybe I'm thinking of this too simply
and I'm the farthest thing from a
lawyer, but discovery exists. If you get
sued civily and stuff,
>> you get access to everything
>> and that can get leaked.
>> Mhm.
>> So why it often does,
>> right? So these people being so arrogant
>> to be like, "Ah, no one will ever know
that I had 11,500
emails with the dude, so I'll keep my
job at Goldman Sachs."
>> Incredible. Yeah, it's crazy.
>> What goes through somebody's mind? Like,
she knew how many emails I mean, she at
least in her mind had a ballpark figure.
>> Kathy Rumler.
>> Kathy Rumler. how many emails she
exchanged with with Jeffrey Epstein and
did she think that by not telling the
seauite at Goldman Sachs that it just
wasn't going to be a problem that this
was never going to come to light? I
mean, the guy died in 2019.
It's 2026
and it never occurred to her, you know,
maybe I should try to get ahead of this.
>> This is going to be a problem.
or was she that arrogant to think that
she could just weather this?
>> And you know, if if you're the CEO of if
you're the CEO of Goldman Sachs, you
have to be saying, "Fucking Rumbler,
what was she thinking?"
>> Yeah. I mean, he should have done that
though three years ago.
>> Yeah, he should have. Yes.
>> He should have just cut ties with these
people.
>> Mhm. you know,
like when it when it when they're in
that kind of position, it gets weird
when he's like friends with or
associating with guys in academia and
stuff like that because you're like,
well, you know, funders come in and fund
stuff.
>> Mhm.
>> And now we see a lot of that was a lot
closer than that to be clear. But like
when you're a lawyer at the Obama
Justice Department, like the lawyer or
in the Obama White House and you have
that kind of access and you were dealing
with this guy a ton who you know
is a spy now.
Mhm.
You have to know you're going to be
fried in this. It's there's just no way
to look at it. And if you've got the
kind of money that the general counsel
at Goldman Sachs would have, then you
hire a reputation
recovery firm,
right? And they're out there,
reputation.com
for, you know, average people like you
and me
>> or Peggy Seagull.
>> Or Peggy Seagull,
>> and get ahead of this. [sighs]
>> Yeah.
>> And And I don't think anybody
thought to do that.
>> They did not. Mhm. [clears throat] And
it's very clear that Jeffrey maintained
all of his power or I should say almost
all of his powerful contacts including
new ones post conviction. You know,
that's the oddest thing to me was that
conviction. This is a child sex crime
conviction.
As
entry level as it was for him because of
the sweetheart deal,
you think that that would send people
screaming from the room and it didn't.
It didn't set him back at all. He just
jumped right in. Right back in. No
problem.
What do you think the angle with Bannon
was looking at this? Because Bannon
leaves the White House with Trump after
he's fired.
>> And then from all the texts we can see,
which are cringe, the emails we can see,
he is essentially becoming that PR guy.
>> Yeah, he is
>> for Jeffrey Epstein. He even has an
email in there where he's like,
>> "You have a [__] jihad against you."
The likes of which I've never seen and
I've seen a lot of [__] And then, you
know, they're following up emails on
here where he's sending Jeffree articles
and saying, "Well, this makes you sound
like you're contrite." and you know
talking about all this stuff and then he
films them on camera for what was
reported to be up to 18 hours worth of
footage. We have like 2 to four hours of
it or something through the files. You
know this is a guy Bannon who like I
said goes way back to the 80s with all
these people. Is he is he a spy? Like
I've always believed that. Do you think
that's plausible?
Plausible? Sure. Likely I I can't
imagine
>> why
>> because at the position that he was
counselor to the president, he would
have been vetted should have been vetted
nine ways from Sunday. He should have
been the FBI should have been all over
this. Of course, you know my position on
the FBI. So,
>> um,
>> but Howard, you say that Howard Luck
makes the Congress advisor Leon Black's
Leon Black's son works in the [__]
administration. Like, these are vetting
101.
>> Yeah, you're right. You're right. Sure.
It's plausible. I'm trying to think what
the hook would be, what what the
what the vulnerability would be to
recruit him because Bannon's almost a
billionaire,
>> right? He owns the rights to Seinfeld
and a whole bunch of other things. He's
worth the last I saw several years ago,
he was worth $750 million. So, you're
not going to recruit him with money.
>> Unless he was recruited before he got it
>> unless Okay, that's a good point.
>> He always ends up in places. That's the
thing. He's always in the right place.
>> He's long been in the right place at the
right time. There was one phone call I
was on with a guy who was talking my ear
off back in 2022
that I another one of those like shiver
up the spines because this was after I
had read the Abbott piece. I was on to
this with Steve Bannon and this dude was
listing off a whole bunch of things and
he starts talking about this guy Brock
Mighty Ducks Brock guy. Can we Google
that? Brock uh
>> Brock Pierce.
>> Brock Pierce. You know about Brock
Pierce? No,
>> Brock Pierce is worth a [__] ton of
money. Made it. He was an Mighty Ducks
actor. Ends up I'm going to really
shorten this up for people, but he ends
up in a partnership business-wise with
this guy who ends up having these
parties out in Hollywood where they the
the guy is is
boys, underage boys.
>> My god.
>> And that ends up coming out and then
they all flee to Spain. That guy ends up
getting arrested. He stands I think he
stands trial or makes a deal or
something and then eventually gets
permission to leave the country for some
sort of surgery and never comes back and
gets a new name.
>> But Rock,
can you pull up as Wikipedia def cuz now
it's in there and this is starting to
like break open. I've been telling
people to pull on this, but go down. Def
Brock ends up up a little more,
more,
more, more. Right. And
up a little more. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So,
Brock ends up founding in 2001. Now, I'm
going right off Wikipedia, people. He
founded internet gaming entertainment, a
company that pioneered the MMORPG
currency selling services industry.
Between 04 and05, IG spent more than $25
million buying out seven smaller
competitors, including four auction
platforms and many fan and content
sites. In in ' 05, PICE estimated the
accounted for about 50% of this online
market in the US, which has about $500
million in annual volume. Pierce brought
in Steve Bannon, formerly of Goldman
Sachs and Breitbart News, to seek
venture capital, and a deal was made in
February 2006, yielding 60 million, of
which Pierce took away 20 million for a
minority stake. The next year, the
company faced a class action lawsuit
with no assets. The company failed and
Pierce was conveniently forced out. Now,
go down to the Epstein section, Def.
In February 2026, an investigation by
the Kev Independent and newly released
US Department of Justice documents on
Jeffrey Epstein reported that the files
included an email in which a man
identified his peers, described as a
co-founder of Tether, told Epstein that
a boat in Antigua full of amazing uh
Ukraine's finest was waiting for him. A
separate analysis of the same document
released by the crypto news outlet Proto
stated that in 2012 after Epstein asked
Pierce to take photos and find me a
present during a trip to Moscow, Kev,
and Odessa, which is where they would
source a lot of underage women and
traffic them. By the way, PICE emailed
Epstein's dozens of photographs of the
Ukrainian woman named Anastasia and
closed the message by writing that
Ukraine is now my favorite country. And
in another email, he invited Epstein to
join him on a boat in Antigua. Once
again, full of Ukraine's finest. This is
stuff that is now new online that I was
told in 2002 directly about this. And
just conveniently, this guy before he
even blows up, he was a Mighty Ducks
actor. Before he blows up as a
businessman and before, like this person
I was on the phone with also told me
about his Jeffrey Epstein connections as
well. before that he just happens to
bring in Steve Bannon to this video game
community that also then this is where
it gets above my pay grade but it has
and pull that mic around because I want
you to say what you're going to say but
it has to do with moving money online
that's like through video game coins
that can be laundered into other stuff
maybe people out there can help me but
go ahead
>> I was going to say because it was a big
thing that China had first gotten
involved with with the video game
Runescape they'd sell in-game currency
for real money but this is weird And I'm
only going to bring this point up for
you to pull on if you want. This whole
conspiracy that they keep seeing all
this activity from Epstein's account on
Fortnite and all these video games.
Just think that's a weird little
connection now to know that Bannon was
involved with that. Just saying. I don't
know.
>> Yeah, that's crazy.
>> It's weird.
>> I don't know, man. And he's still very
much an insider in Washington. He's got
his podcast. He's got a house on Capitol
Hill.
>> He's the war room. Yep.
>> Yeah.
>> What do we do? Do you just blow it all
up?
>> You know what? We're going to have to
we're going to have to
like even if it means taking to the
streets, demand the release of all the
remaining documents. We have to. They
have to be released. First of all, the
law mandates that they be released. It's
not at the pan body or anybody else.
They have to be released. That's the
law.
And then we need to rely on people like
you
to go through these things and make
sense of them.
How about all the code words they're
using?
>> Yeah. See, now that's another thing.
See, and this is we're weakened by the
fact that we can't charge people with
crimes. You know, imagine how easy how
much easier it would be
to say, "Look, you're involved in this.
We've got a conspiracy charge hanging
over you. You're going to do at least 5
years
or you can tell us what all these code
words mean and walk us through this one
step at a time and then we'll figure
out, you know, something a little
easier."
But DOJ can't do that.
There's one that's used in there that
DeF and I were looking at this morning
and you know your brain runs in a lot of
different directions where it says jerky
and there was a guy who did a nice
breakdown of this de let me give you
this dude I actually have it right here
so I want to give him a shout out this
is Dr. G explains
on YouTube. And what I liked is he
didn't he even when it was obvious where
it's like, all right, we can definitely
make some sort of like this type of
conclusion there. He didn't. He just
reported the [__] emails.
But
the way they're they refer to we need
more jerky. We need to put it in the
fridge. We need this number of pounds of
it. We
>> have to cook it. This email right here
that de pulled up says, "How is your
jerky situation? Should I bring any
more?" And there's another email to
Jeffrey Epstein from Unknown. Francis
has time to come tomorrow to show me how
to make it. Jerky class, anyone? It will
also
he will also bring you a taste of his
new jerky recipe from the restaurant and
sends a warm hello. He is working at a
restaurant called Cannibal and Cooks. Is
this real?
>> This is from Jmail.
>> Wait for it. Beef jerky and steak. He
has time at 3 PM tomorrow if this is
okay with you. And they refer to like,
didn't they refer to storing it like
chemically?
>> No. In freezers.
>> In free. Yeah.
>> That's why I thought blood.
>> I mean,
>> see, this is why we need the rest of
these documents.
>> The whole thing is a 4chan.
>> Yeah. A dream.
>> Yeah.
I will freely admit it.
>> You're right.
>> Yeah,
>> they did what?
>> Steve sent me some.
>> There's also an Epstein connection to
the creator of 4chan quote moot
>> and how No, you're good. And how he and
Bannon helped to create
>> politics
>> r/politics which basically create
created the alt-right pipeline that
helped Trump win the election.
>> [snorts]
>> It just goes deeper and deeper and
deeper. Okay. Can you pull up the Peter
Teal Brexit email exchange?
>> Yeah.
>> With with with Epstein 2016. June 2016.
>> It's probably not in
>> I I have this one about the collapse. Is
that what you're talking about?
>> Yes. Okay. So, Epstein, you know what's
crazy, bro? I remember. Oh god, that's
so weird. I remember where I was when
this happened, too. This wasn't that far
away. Okay, so Brexit, he sends to Peter
Teal, Brexit, just the beginning. Peter
Teal responds of what? And Epstein goes,
"Return to tribalism, counter to
globalization, amazing new alliances.
You and I both agreed zero interest
rates were too high. And as I said in
your office, finding things on their way
to collapse was much easier than finding
the next bargain.
This is where the whole bankers
profitering off of war. And obviously
Peter Teal is not a banker. Jeffrey
worked in finance for bankers and stuff,
but like they're from the banker class,
if you will. This is where I look at
that and go, well, here you go.
Wow.
Oh my god.
>> I never seen you so speechless this
much.
>> I feel bad that I'm so shocked that I
can't contribute very much. [laughter]
It's so overwhelming. It's so sickening.
I I didn't realize it was this deep.
Incredible.
And you know, Jeffrey Epstein aside, and
Glenn Maxwell, of course, these are the
people that are still running the
country.
>> Yes.
>> Literally,
>> they're running the economy.
>> Notice the vice president hasn't said
anything.
>> Not a word.
>> Recently,
>> not a single word.
>> That's his chief funer right there.
>> Yes, it is.
>> He also had a
>> He created JD Vance.
>> Yes. But actually before that, are you
aware that JD Vance had a fundraiser
dinner at Les Wexner's house in 2017?
that I I was not aware, but that
actually doesn't surprise me.
>> It doesn't?
>> No, because Les Wexter was the guy in
Columbus, Ohio. And if you're a
Republican in Ohio, you need to kiss the
ring.
>> Yeah.
I did not know it though.
if remove our own guilt in this for a
second because we definitely have some
that I I do believe and again I'm very
open to changing my opinion on things
but I do believe
>> in this situation CIA and US
intelligence has blood on its hands with
all this. I I just don't see a scenario
where they don't. But you also
>> have other governments that do as well.
>> Yes.
>> And it's it's multiple. It's an ally
like the UK. Mhm.
>> It's an ally like Israel where we know
Jeffrey had significant contacts
including Ahoud Barack. It also came out
in the emails that the US
>> uh the the Israeli UN security team came
over to install all of his security at
his place. Oh, you didn't see. Can we
pull up this email?
>> Are you kidding me?
>> John's having a [__] crisis of
conscious right now. I'm sorry.
There's been a lot of me talking the
last half hour while John's just like
questioning everything. [laughter]
>> All right, so this is from Mario Nall.
Israeli government
>> Oh, I just talked to Mario two days ago.
>> No, there you go. The chances. Israeli
government installed security systems at
Epstein's Manhattan building where he
housed underage models. Starting 2016,
Israeli mission to the UN coordinated
with Epstein's staff to install alarm
sensors and surveillance equipment. Rafi
Schlommo, who you know, I said this
earlier, very Russian name.
>> Head of security for former Israeli PM
Audac personally controlled access to
the apartment, did background checks on
cleaners, remotely disabled alarms when
people needed to enter, and Epstein
personally improved it all. The emails
are right there. I read these in the
solo episode the other day, but this
this tweets up on the screen. Just if
you wouldn't mind, DeF just pulling up
the email so people can see it.
>> But this is the back and forth. And then
the other one, I think also this is
where they're going through the details,
but then this is where it's laid out
with the Hood's name in there and
everything. I believe Neilia Hood was on
the other email, his wife, I assume, but
they're going through the whole things
of what they're going to be wiring. And
it seems like they have a pretty chummy
relationship.
>> It sure seems that way. And Jeffrey
doesn't mind holes in the walls. Of
course, we learned that in spades at the
island house.
Wow, man.
>> Did you see Netanyahu's
response to
>> no
>> the Ahoud Barack?
>> I'd love to hear it.
I'm paraphrasing here, but he said,
"This actually proves that we are not
guilty because Audac has attempted to
overthrow the entire Israeli order as a
political opponent for many years and
operated." I don't know if he said in
like the George Soros crowd or something
like that, but he was like insinuating
like, you know, anti-Israel. And we're
talking about a dude to Hub Barack who
does have opposite politics in many
cases. Yeah. to Netanyahu except in the
case of, you know, trying to grow
Israel, which, you know, that's that's
what they're trying to do. How they do
that is certainly the question. But, you
know,
>> to say that about a dude who is like
within Israel, a legendary special
forces guy.
>> Yeah.
>> Who got it? We have that the [__] New
York City shot from the movie Munich
right there where he gets a shout out in
the [__] movie
>> while they're doing while Msada is doing
some of the [__] right? And [snorts]
then he becomes prime minister
eventually, defense minister and
everything.
>> But being with Epste is a way to show
>> that you're innocent. That seems a
little
>> No, he's flailing around,
>> right?
>> Unbelievable.
>> Is it an uncservivable
because of the public's reaction if that
information were flatout confirmed by
both governments? Is it an unservivable
act for an allyship between the two
nations? No,
>> it's not.
>> No, no. This is going to be a little
blip. A temporary blip. Oh, listen.
The Israelis.
The the pro-Israel lobby, mostly in the
form of Apac, is so entrenched in
American politics, American society,
American culture
that the relationship isn't changing at
all. It's only because of the likes of
of Tucker Carlson,
people with large followings out there
speaking truth and talking about what
America first really means.
>> That might make a difference. People are
going to they're going to say, "Oh, well
that Barack, well, first of all, he's a
has been. Secondly, h you know, that was
a long time ago. It's almost 10 years
ago, and it's not Netanyahu. Netanyahu
is the one in charge now. That's going
to be the reaction.
But the public is so aware of some of
these things though now because of many
people on the left and right. It's a
very bipartisan thing.
>> Very much so. Yes. And so you think even
in this kind of year it would be a blip
if we found out that had some sort of
confirmation that the most prolific
known public pedophile spy dude, arms
dealer, trilateral commission person,
Coney Island resident, you know,
>> was running a msad honeypot operation
with all the above and money laundering.
>> We just moved. They they didn't they
didn't care for more than a few weeks
when Jonathan Pard was caught red-handed
and they were managing the operation
from the Israeli defense minister's
office.
>> Rafi was overseeing it, I believe.
>> Right. Um it didn't matter and the
Israelis hemmed and hawed and then kind
of quietly apologized and everything
just kind of roared right back. And I
think that's we're going to see again.
So, here's the other thing a lot of
people say online and I and I understand
why they say it, but I have you in the
studio right now as someone who used to
be in the intelligence community who can
speak to this, but people will often say
CIA equals MSAD, MSAD equals CIA.
>> It's just simply not true.
>> Okay.
>> That that's a statement made out of
ignorance.
>> Yeah.
>> Now, why why do you say that?
>> Because I agree with you from what
you've told me, but I'd love for you to
explain it to everybody. the because the
Mossad actively spies on the United
States. Actively.
Yes, we have a close operational
relationship with Mossad. But to say
we're two peas in a pod like that,
absolutely not true. We are with the
Brits, the Canadians, the Australians,
the New Zealanders, the Five Eyes
countries. We have very close relations
with several other, you know, NATO
countries. But the Israelis, listen, at
the CIA,
Israel was ranked as critical threat for
counter intelligence along with Russia,
China, Cuba, and North Korea.
Yeah, the Israelis are not our friends.
They actively recruit Americans to spy
on Israel's behalf, to betray the United
States. Now, the people who make those
arguments though, one place where I
could see from their lens is when you
look at the top of the chain with say
directors of these agencies who are
political appointees, you have a guy
like Mike Pompeo who ran CIA who could
not possibly be more pro-Israel, right?
>> Not possible to be more pro- Israel than
Mike Pompeo. So is it possible that
there are some pockets
>> where there is some overlap but for the
most part as you're saying the rank and
file and people who work at the agencies
they don't really like each other.
>> Sure. Yeah. It's it's possible to say
that and you know presidents come and go
administrations change the the
relationship is
is you know
fraternal
>> right
>> at the working level it's not so nice
[clears throat]
>> the last thing today John this this has
been good but I know I'm some of this is
like
>> I'm intellectually exhausted now I'm
very upset by all this
>> I can see so [laughter] I I I don't
I don't want to
>> like what happened to our country.
>> I don't want to torture you,
>> but I do have to get to the one thing
that we left off from the beginning,
which is what you heard about the whole
Iran thing. I'm not going to say
anything. I'm just going to let you go
with whatever you're allowed to say. So,
I have I have a friend uh former CIA
officer who was at the White House this
morning talking to his friends and he
says that a decision has been made to
attack Iran on Monday or Tuesday. The
president yesterday gave the Iranians 10
days to uh to you know accept our
proposals for an end to their ballistic
missile program, an end to to uh their
uranium enrichment program, an end to
supporting um groups in the Middle East
like Hamas and Hezbollah and the
Houthis.
But he's done this before. Well, he'll
he'll give you 10 days, he'll give you
two weeks, and then he'll just attack
two days into it. He thinks that that
keeps people off balance. Um, the USS
Abraham Lincoln has been in the Arabian
Sea for weeks. We've got about two dozen
support ships in the Persian Gulf, the
Arabian Sea, the Red Sea, and the
Eastern Mediterranean. We've got the USS
Gerald Ford, which is
>> in Gibralar right now. It's it's passing
through the straits of Gibralar like
today on its way to uh the Eastern
Mediterranean and probably through the
Suez Canal into the Red Sea. So we've
we're going to have enough assets to
attack Iran in the next couple of days.
And so he said that there are battle
lines that the anti-
war forces are JD Vance and Tulsi
Gabbard. He said that the pro that's it.
He said, "The pro-war people are led by
Marco Rubio and include Pete Hegsth and
now the Joint Chiefs of Staff." And I I
stopped him on that point this morning
and I said, "Wait a minute." I said,
"During the Iraq war, at the start of
the Iraq war, the most stridently
anti-war
component was the Joint Chiefs of Staff.
They were always the last ones that
wanted to attack because they know what
war is." and he said, "Ah, but you
forget Trump has replaced all of the
joint chiefs this year, this past in the
past 12 months," which I had forgotten.
Any of these four-star generals who, you
know, had worked their way up through
the ranks, but had served under Biden,
he fired all of them.
All of them. And he promoted people that
he knew would be politically loyal. M
>> so I you know Julian I I've always been
one of these glass half full guys. I'm
I'm
>> Me too.
>> I've always been optimistic about things
and I've been saying a lot in my own
podcasts in written pieces. You know we
we went through round one with the
Omanis in Muscat. We went through round
two with Swiss in Geneva. Both sides
came out and said, "These were both
productive uh meetings. We're going to
go to round three. Everything's looking
good. The Omanis are asking us to just
relax and let them do what they're good
at." The Omanis are really, really good
at diplomacy. Really good. They're very,
very good friends. Um,
and they're honest, so the Iranians
trust them as well. And I think that
none of that really matters right now. I
think a decision's been made. Do you
think this is to distract from the
current scandal? Uh,
>> probably in part. Yeah.
>> How about them saying they're going to
release the UFO files last night, which
I've wanted released forever, but
>> I know, right? I mean, we've been
talking about this for years.
>> The timing.
>> Yeah.
Yes.
[sighs]
>> Yep.
>> Same movie over and over again.
Different actors, just remakes. And you
remember, you're probably a little bit
too young, but in the '90s, the movie
Wag the Dog was like, you know, people
had their hair on fire. Oh my god, that
look, this movie is about the president
made a war to distract from his affair.
It's like, yeah, how quaint that is now.
>> So quaint.
>> That seems to be all that happens. And
people have short memories.
>> Well, I hope that I I will take that
clip and put that out tomorrow,
Saturday. so that we can
maybe get some attention on that to see
if somehow that little ripple ends up
making its way to change some decisions
because
>> one of the promises of of of Trump's
campaign was no more endless wars,
right?
>> Going into Iran is entirely different
than going into Venezuela.
>> 92 million people. It's a gigantic
country. It's bigger than Texas and it
has 92 million people. And I think that
at the White House, they have just they
have just bitten right into this Israeli
propaganda,
the same kind of propaganda we got in
2003, that as soon as we cross that
border, they're going to throw flowers
at us and they're going to greet us as
liberators and we're all going to live
happily ever after and everybody's going
to get rich on the new oil deals. And
that's just not going to happen. It
never happens.
Crazy
world, John.
>> It is, man.
>> Well, I'm sorry to blow your mind a few
times today.
>> I was I'm not often stunned into
speechlessness.
>> You also blew my mind as regular,
though. That happens every single time.
Like you just that your life experiences
are insane. And I'm really, you know,
jokes aside with the memes. So happy to
see you
>> getting the attention you deserved and
have deserved for a long time for people
that
>> are just learning about John
>> online. Your story had a long very
unfair downswing to it that you know
>> it's been an odyssey that's for sure.
>> Getting back we all get a good laugh,
you know, out of these memes, but this
this was deadly serious.
>> Oh yeah, no doubt about it. But I'm I'm
really happy to see it and we'll
continue supporting it here.
>> Good to see you again. It's great to see
you as always, sir.
>> Thank you.
>> All right,
>> take care.
>> Everybody else, you know what it is.
Give it a thought. Get back to me.
Hopefully, we're not at war with [__]
Iran. Peace. Thank you as always for
watching this video, guys. If you have
not already subscribed, please hit that
subscribe button as well as that like
button before you leave. See you for the
next episode.